<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BedtimeStories</string>
    <string name="story0text">A shepherd-boy, who watched a flock of sheep near a village, brought out the villagers three or four times by crying out, \"Wolf! Wolf!\" and when his neighbors came to help him, laughed at them for their pains.\n\nThe Wolf, however, did truly come at last. The Shepherd-boy, now really alarmed, shouted in an agony of terror: \"Pray, do come and help me; the Wolf is killing the sheep\"; but no one paid any heed to his cries, nor rendered any assistance. The Wolf, having no cause of fear, at his leisure lacerated or destroyed the whole flock.\n\nThere is no believing a liar, even when he speaks the truth.</string>
    <string name="story1text">An old man on the point of death summoned his sons around him to give them some parting advice. He ordered his servants to bring in a bundle of sticks, and said to his eldest son, \"Break it.\" The son strained and strained, but with all his efforts was unable to break the bundle. The other sons also tried, but none of them was successful. \"Untie the bundle,\" said the father, \"and each of you take a stick.\" When they had done so, he called out to them, \"Now, break,\" and each stick was easily broken. \"You see my meaning,\" said their father.</string>
    <string name="story2text">A Fox once saw a Crow fly off with a piece of cheese in its beak and settle on a branch of a tree.\n\n\"That\'s for me, as I am a Fox,\" said Master Reynard, and he walked up to the foot of the tree.\n\n\"Good day, Mistress Crow,\" he cried. \"How well you are looking today: how glossy your feathers; how bright your eye. I feel sure your voice must surpass that of other birds, just as your figure does; let me hear but one song from you that I may greet you as the Queen of Birds.\"\n\nThe Crow lifted up her head and began to caw her best, but the moment she opened her mouth the piece of cheese fell to the ground, only to be snapped up by Master Fox.\n\n\"That will do,\" said he. \"That was all I wanted. In exchange for your cheese I will give you a piece of advice for the future: \"Do not trust flatterers.\"</string>
    <string name="story3text">A Lion lay asleep in the forest, his great head resting on his paws. A timid little Mouse came upon him unexpectedly, and in her fright and haste to get away, ran across the Lion\'s nose. Roused from his nap, the Lion laid his huge paw angrily on the tiny creature to kill her.\n\n\"Spare me!\" begged the poor Mouse. \"Please let me go and some day I will surely repay you.\"\n\nThe Lion was much amused to think that a Mouse could ever help him. But he was generous and finally let the Mouse go.\n\nSome days later, while stalking his prey in the forest, the Lion was caught in the toils of a hunter\'s net. Unable to free himself, he filled the forest with his angry roaring. The Mouse knew the voice and quickly found the Lion struggling in the net. Running to one of the great ropes that bound him, she gnawed it until it parted, and soon the Lion was free.\n\n\"You laughed when I said I would repay you,\" said the Mouse. \"Now you see that even a Mouse can help a Lion.\"\n\nMoral: A kindness is never wasted.</string>
    <string name="story4text">A Hare was making fun of the Tortoise one day for being so slow.\n\n\"Do you ever get anywhere?\" he asked with a mocking laugh.\n\n\"Yes,\" replied the Tortoise, \"and I get there sooner than you think. I\'ll run you a race and prove it.\"\n\nThe Hare was much amused at the idea of running a race with the Tortoise, but for the fun of the thing he agreed. So the Fox, who had consented to act as judge, marked the distance and started the runners off.\n\nThe Hare was soon far out of sight, and to make the Tortoise feel very deeply how ridiculous it was for him to try a race with a Hare, he lay down beside the course to take a nap until the Tortoise should catch up.\n\n\nThe Tortoise meanwhile kept going slowly but steadily, and, after a time, passed the place where the Hare was sleeping. But the Hare slept on very peacefully; and when at last he did wake up, the Tortoise was near the goal. The Hare now ran his swiftest, but he could not overtake the Tortoise in time.\n\nMoral: The race is not always to the swift.</string>
    <string name="story5text">The Wind and the Sun were disputing which was the stronger. Suddenly they saw a traveller coming down the road, and the Sun said, \"I see a way to decide our dispute. Whichever of us can cause that traveller to take off his cloak shall be regarded as the stronger. You begin.\" So the Sun retired behind a cloud, and the Wind began to blow as hard as it could upon the traveller. But the harder he blew the more closely did the traveller wrap his cloak round him, till at last the Wind had to give up in despair. Then the Sun came out and shone in all his glory upon the traveller, who soon found it too hot to walk with his cloak on.</string>
    <string name="story6text">A certain Wolf could not get enough to eat because of the watchfulness of the Shepherds. But one night he found a sheep skin that had been cast aside and forgotten. The next day, dressed in the skin, the Wolf strolled into the pasture with the Sheep. Soon a little Lamb was following him about and was quickly led away to slaughter.\n\nThat evening the Wolf entered the fold with the flock. But it happened that the Shepherd took a fancy for mutton broth that very evening, and, picking up a knife, went to the fold. There the first he laid hands on and killed was the Wolf.\n\nMoral: The evil doer often comes to harm through his own deceit.</string>
    <string name="story7text">Once upon a time there was a dear little girl who was loved by everyone who looked at her, but most of all by her grandmother, and there was nothing that she would not have given to the child. Once she gave her a little riding hood of red velvet, which suited her so well that she would never wear anything else; so she was always called \'Little Red Riding Hood.\'\n\nOne day her mother said to her: \'Come, Little Red Riding Hood, here is a piece of cake and a bottle of wine; take them to your grandmother, she is ill and weak, and they will do her good. Set out before it gets hot, and when you are going, walk nicely and quietly and do not run off the path, or you may fall and break the bottle, and then your grandmother will get nothing; and when you go into her room, don\'t forget to say, \"Good morning\", and don\'t peep into every corner before you do it.\'\n\n\'I will take great care,\' said Little Red Riding Hood to her mother, and gave her hand on it.\n\nThe grandmother lived out in the wood, half a league from the village, and just as Little Red Riding Hood entered the wood, a wolf met her. Red Riding Hood did not know what a wicked creature he was, and was not at all afraid of him.\n\n\'Good day, Little Red Riding Hood,\' said he.\n\n\'Thank you kindly, wolf.\'\n\n\'Whither away so early, Little Red Riding Hood?\'\n\n\'To my grandmother\'s.\'\n\n\'What have you got in your apron?\'\n\n\'Cake and wine; yesterday was baking-day, so poor sick grandmother is to have something good, to make her stronger.\'\n\n\'Where does your grandmother live, Little Red Riding Hood?\'\n\n\'A good quarter of a league farther on in the wood; her house stands under the three large oak-trees, the nut-trees are just below; you surely must know it,\' replied Little Red Riding Hood.\n\nThe wolf thought to himself: \'What a tender young creature! what a nice plump mouthful - she will be better to eat than the old woman. I must act craftily, so as to catch both.\'\n\nSo he walked for a short time by the side of Little Red Riding Hood, and then he said: \'See, Little Red Riding Hood, how pretty the flowers are about here - why do you not look round? I believe, too, that you do not hear how sweetly the little birds are singing; you walk gravely along as if you were going to school, while everything else out here in the wood is merry.\'\n\nLittle Red Riding Hood raised her eyes, and when she saw the sunbeams dancing here and there through the trees, and pretty flowers growing everywhere, she thought: \'Suppose I take grandmother a fresh nosegay; that would please her too. It is so early in the day that I shall still get there in good time.\'\n\nSo she ran from the path into the wood to look for flowers. And whenever she had picked one, she fancied that she saw a still prettier one farther on, and ran after it, and so got deeper and deeper into the wood.\n\nMeanwhile the wolf ran straight to the grandmother\'s house and knocked at the door.\n\n\'Who is there?\'\n\n\'Little Red Riding Hood,\' replied the wolf. \'She is bringing cake and wine; open the door.\'\n\n\'Lift the latch,\' called out the grandmother, \'I am too weak, and cannot get up.\'\n\nThe wolf lifted the latch, the door sprang open, and without saying a word he went straight to the grandmother\'s bed, and devoured her. Then he put on her clothes, dressed himself in her cap, laid himself in bed and drew the curtains.\n\nLittle Red Riding Hood, however, had been running about picking flowers, and when she had gathered so many that she could carry no more, she remembered her grandmother, and set out on the way to her.\n\nShe was surprised to find the cottage-door standing open, and when she went into the room, she had such a strange feeling that she said to herself: \'Oh dear! how uneasy I feel today, and at other times I like being with grandmother so much.\' She called out: \'Good morning,\' but received no answer; so she went to the bed and drew back the curtains. There lay her grandmother with her cap pulled far over her face, and looking very strange.\n\n\'Oh! grandmother,\' she said, \'what big ears you have!\'\n\n\'All the better to hear you with, my child,\' was the reply.\n\n\'But, grandmother, what big eyes you have!\' she said.\n\n\'All the better to see you with, my dear.\'\n\n\'But, grandmother, what large hands you have!\'\n\n\'All the better to hug you with.\'\n\n\'Oh! but, grandmother, what a terrible big mouth you have!\'\n\n\'All the better to eat you with!\'\n\nAnd scarcely had the wolf said this, than with one bound he was out of bed and swallowed up Red Riding Hood.\n\nWhen the wolf had appeased his appetite, he lay down again in the bed, fell asleep and began to snore very loud.\n\nThe huntsman was just passing the house, and thought to himself: \'How the old woman is snoring! I must just see if she wants anything.\' So he went into the room, and when he came to the bed, he saw that the wolf was lying in it.\n\n\'Do I find you here, you old sinner!\' said he. \'I have long sought you!\' But just as he was going to fire at him, it occurred to him that the wolf might have devoured the grandmother, and that she might still be saved, so he did not fire, but took a pair of scissors, and began to cut open the stomach of the sleeping wolf.\n\nWhen he had made two snips, he saw the little red riding hood shining, and then he made two snips more, and the little girl sprang out, crying: \'Ah, how frightened I have been! How dark it was inside the wolf.\'\n\nAfter that the aged grandmother came out alive also, but scarcely able to breathe. Red Riding Hood, however, quickly fetched great stones with which they filled the wolf\'s belly, and when he awoke, he wanted to run away, but the stones were so heavy that he collapsed at once, and fell dead.\n\nThen all three were delighted. The huntsman drew off the wolf\'s skin and went home with it; the grandmother ate the cake and drank the wine which Red Riding Hood had brought, and revived. But Red Riding Hood thought to herself: \'As long as I live, I will never leave the path by myself to run into the wood, when my mother has forbidden me to do so.\'\n\nIt is also related that once, when Red Riding Hood was again taking cakes to the old grandmother, another wolf spoke to her, and tried to entice her from the path. Red Riding Hood, however, was on her guard, and went straight forward on her way, and told her grandmother that she had met the wolf, and that he had said \'good morning\' to her, but with such a wicked look in his eyes, that if they had not been on the public road she was certain he would have eaten her up.\n\n\'Well,\' said the grandmother, \'we will shut the door, so that he can not come in.\'\n\nSoon afterwards the wolf knocked, and cried: \'Open the door, grandmother, I am Little Red Riding Hood, and am bringing you some cakes.\'\n\nBut they did not speak, or open the door, so the grey-beard stole twice or thrice round the house, and at last jumped on the roof, intending to wait until Red Riding Hood went home in the evening, and then to steal after her and devour her in the darkness. But the grandmother saw what was in his thoughts.\n\nIn front of the house was a great stone trough, so she said to the child: \'Take the pail, Red Riding Hood; I made some sausages yesterday, so carry the water in which I boiled them to the trough.\'\n\nRed Riding Hood carried until the great trough was quite full. Then the smell of the sausages reached the wolf, and he sniffed and peeped down, and at last stretched out his neck so far that he could no longer keep his footing and began to slip, and slipped down from the roof straight into the great trough, and was drowned. But Red Riding Hood went joyously home, and no one ever did anything to harm her again.</string>
    <string name="story8text">There were once a man and a woman who had long, in vain, wished for a child. At length it appeared that God was about to grant their desire.\n\nThese people had a little window at the back of their house from which a splendid garden could be seen, which was full of the most beautiful flowers and herbs. It was, however, surrounded by a high wall, and no one dared to go into it because it belonged to an enchantress, who had great power and was dreaded by all the world.\n\nOne day the woman was standing by this window and looking down into the garden, when she saw a bed which was planted with the most beautiful rampion, and it looked so fresh and green that she longed for it. She quite pined away, and began to look pale and miserable.\n\nHer husband was alarmed, and asked: \'What ails you, dear wife?\'\n\n\'Ah,\' she replied, \'if I can\'t eat some of the rampion, which is in the garden behind our house, I shall die.\'\n\nThe man, who loved her, thought: \'Sooner than let your wife die, bring her some of the rampion yourself, let it cost what it will.\'\n\nAt twilight, he clambered down over the wall into the garden of the enchantress, hastily clutched a handful of rampion, and took it to his wife. She at once made herself a salad of it, and ate it greedily. It tasted so good to her - so very good, that the next day she longed for it three times as much as before.\n\nIf he was to have any rest, her husband knew he must once more descend into the garden. Therefore, in the gloom of evening, he let himself down again; but when he had clambered down the wall he was terribly afraid, for he saw the enchantress standing before him.\n\n\'How can you dare,\' said she with angry look, \'descend into my garden and steal my rampion like a thief? You shall suffer for it!\'\n\n\'Ah,\' answered he, \'let mercy take the place of justice, I only made up my mind to do it out of necessity. My wife saw your rampion from the window, and felt such a longing for it that she would have died if she had not got some to eat.\'\n\nThe enchantress allowed her anger to be softened, and said to him: \'If the case be as you say, I will allow you to take away with you as much rampion as you will, only I make one condition, you must give me the child which your wife will bring into the world; it shall be well treated, and I will care for it like a mother.\'\n\nThe man in his terror consented to everything.\n\nWhen the woman was brought to bed, the enchantress appeared at once, gave the child the name of Rapunzel, and took it away with her.\n\nRapunzel grew into the most beautiful child under the sun. When she was twelve years old, the enchantress shut her into a tower in the middle of a forest. The tower had neither stairs nor door, but near the top was a little window. When the enchantress wanted to go in, she placed herself beneath it and cried:\n\n\'Rapunzel, Rapunzel,\nLet down your hair to me.\'\nRapunzel had magnificent long hair, fine as spun gold, and when she heard the voice of the enchantress, she unfastened her braided tresses, wound them round one of the hooks of the window above, and then the hair fell twenty ells down, and the enchantress climbed up by it.\n\nAfter a year or two, it came to pass that the king\'s son rode through the forest and passed by the tower. Then he heard a song, which was so charming that he stood still and listened. It was Rapunzel, who in her solitude passed her time in letting her sweet voice resound. The king\'s son wanted to climb up to her, and looked for the door of the tower, but none was to be found. He rode home, but the singing had so deeply touched his heart, that every day he went out into the forest and listened to it.\n\nOnce when he was thus standing behind a tree, he saw that an enchantress came there, and he heard how she cried:\n\n\'Rapunzel, Rapunzel,\nLet down your hair to me.\'\nThen Rapunzel let down the braids of her hair, and the enchantress climbed up to her.\n\n\'If that is the ladder by which one mounts, I too will try my fortune,\' said he, and the next day when it began to grow dark, he went to the tower and cried:\n\n\'Rapunzel, Rapunzel,\nLet down your hair to me.\'\nImmediately the hair fell down and the king\'s son climbed up.\n\nAt first Rapunzel was terribly frightened when a man, such as her eyes had never yet beheld, came to her; but the king\'s son began to talk to her quite like a friend, and told her that his heart had been so stirred that it had let him have no rest, and he had been forced to see her. Then Rapunzel lost her fear, and when he asked her if she would take him for her husband, and she saw that he was young and handsome, she thought: \'He will love me more than old Dame Gothel does\'; and she said yes, and laid her hand in his.\n\nShe said: \'I will willingly go away with you, but I do not know how to get down. Bring with you a skein of silk every time that you come, and I will weave a ladder with it, and when that is ready I will descend, and you will take me on your horse.\'\n\nThey agreed that until that time he should come to her every evening, for the old woman came by day. The enchantress remarked nothing of this, until once Rapunzel said to her: \'Tell me, Dame Gothel, how it happens that you are so much heavier for me to draw up than the young king\'s son - he is with me in a moment.\'\n\n\'Ah! you wicked child,\' cried the enchantress. \'What do I hear you say! I thought I had separated you from all the world, and yet you have deceived me!\'\n\nIn her anger she clutched Rapunzel\'s beautiful tresses, wrapped them twice round her left hand, seized a pair of scissors with the right, and snip, snap, they were cut off, and the lovely braids lay on the ground. And she was so pitiless that she took poor Rapunzel into a desert where she had to live in great grief and misery.\n\nOn the same day that she cast out Rapunzel, however, the enchantress fastened the braids of hair, which she had cut off, to the hook of the window, and when the king\'s son came and cried:\n\n\'Rapunzel, Rapunzel,\nLet down your hair to me.\'\nShe let the hair down. The king\'s son ascended, but instead of finding his dearest Rapunzel, he found the enchantress, who gazed at him with wicked and venomous looks.\n\n\'Aha!\' she cried mockingly, \'you would fetch your dearest, but the beautiful bird sits no longer singing in the nest; the cat has got it, and will scratch out your eyes as well. Rapunzel is lost to you; you will never see her again.\'\n\nThe king\'s son was beside himself with pain, and in his despair he leapt down from the tower. He escaped with his life, but the thorns into which he fell pierced his eyes.\n\nHe wandered quite blind about the forest, ate nothing but roots and berries, and did naught but lament and weep over the loss of his dearest wife. Thus he roamed about in misery for some years, and at length came to the desert where Rapunzel, with the twins to which she had given birth, a boy and a girl, lived in wretchedness. He heard a voice, and it seemed so familiar to him that he went towards it, and when he approached, Rapunzel knew him and fell on his neck and wept. Two of her tears wetted his eyes and they grew clear again, and he could see with them as before. He led her to his kingdom where he was joyfully received, and they lived for a long time afterwards, happy and contented.</string>
    <string name="story9text">Once there was a miller who was poor, but who had a beautiful daughter. Now it happened that he had to go and speak to the king, and in order to make himself appear important he said to him, \"I have a daughter who can spin straw into gold.\"\n\nThe king said to the miller, \"That is an art which pleases me well, if your daughter is as clever as you say, bring her to-morrow to my palace, and I will put her to the test.\"\n\nAnd when the girl was brought to him he took her into a room which was quite full of straw, gave her a spinning-wheel and a reel, and said, \"Now set to work, and if by to-morrow morning early you have not spun this straw into gold during the night, you must die.\"\n\nThereupon he himself locked up the room, and left her in it alone. So there sat the poor miller\'s daughter, and for the life of her could not tell what to do, she had no idea how straw could be spun into gold, and she grew more and more frightened, until at last she began to weep.\n\nBut all at once the door opened, and in came a little man, and said, \"Good evening, mistress miller, why are you crying so?\"\n\n\"Alas,\" answered the girl, \"I have to spin straw into gold, and I do not know how to do it.\"\n\n\"What will you give me,\" said the manikin, \"if I do it for you?\"\n\n\"My necklace,\" said the girl.\n\nThe little man took the necklace, seated himself in front of the wheel, and whirr, whirr, whirr, three turns, and the reel was full, then he put another on, and whirr, whirr, whirr, three times round, and the second was full too. And so it went on until the morning, when all the straw was spun, and all the reels were full of gold.\n\nBy daybreak the king was already there, and when he saw the gold he was astonished and delighted, but his heart became only more greedy. He had the miller\'s daughter taken into another room full of straw, which was much larger, and commanded her to spin that also in one night if she valued her life. The girl knew not how to help herself, and was crying, when the door opened again, and the little man appeared, and said, \"What will you give me if I spin that straw into gold for you?\"\n\n\"The ring on my finger,\" answered the girl.\n\nThe little man took the ring, again began to turn the wheel, and by morning had spun all the straw into glittering gold.\n\nThe king rejoiced beyond measure at the sight, but still he had not gold enough, and he had the miller\'s daughter taken into a still larger room full of straw, and said, \"You must spin this, too, in the course of this night, but if you succeed, you shall be my wife.\"\n\nEven if she be a miller\'s daughter, thought he, I could not find a richer wife in the whole world.\n\nWhen the girl was alone the manikin came again for the third time, and said, \"What will you give me if I spin the straw for you this time also?\"\n\n\"I have nothing left that I could give,\" answered the girl.\n\n\"Then promise me, if you should become queen, to give me your first child.\"\n\nWho knows whether that will ever happen, thought the miller\'s daughter, and, not knowing how else to help herself in this strait, she promised the manikin what he wanted, and for that he once more spun the straw into gold.\n\nAnd when the king came in the morning, and found all as he had wished, he took her in marriage, and the pretty miller\'s daughter became a queen.\n\nA year after, she brought a beautiful child into the world, and she never gave a thought to the manikin. But suddenly he came into her room, and said, \"Now give me what you promised.\"\n\nThe queen was horror-struck, and offered the manikin all the riches of the kingdom if he would leave her the child. But the manikin said, \"No, something alive is dearer to me than all the treasures in the world.\"\n\nThen the queen began to lament and cry, so that the manikin pitied her.\n\n\"I will give you three days, time,\" said he, \"if by that time you find out my name, then shall you keep your child.\"\n\nSo the queen thought the whole night of all the names that she had ever heard, and she sent a messenger over the country to inquire, far and wide, for any other names that there might be. When the manikin came the next day, she began with Caspar, Melchior, Balthazar, and said all the names she knew, one after another, but to every one the little man said, \"That is not my name.\"\n\nOn the second day she had inquiries made in the neighborhood as to the names of the people there, and she repeated to the manikin the most uncommon and curious. Perhaps your name is Shortribs, or Sheepshanks, or Laceleg, but he always answered, \"That is not my name.\"\n\nOn the third day the messenger came back again, and said, \"I have not been able to find a single new name, but as I came to a high mountain at the end of the forest, where the fox and the hare bid each other good night, there I saw a little house, and before the house a fire was burning, and round about the fire quite a ridiculous little man was jumping, he hopped upon one leg, and shouted –\n\n\'To-day I bake, to-morrow brew,\nthe next I\'ll have the young queen\'s child.\nHa, glad am I that no one knew\nthat Rumpelstiltskin I am styled.\'\"\nYou may imagine how glad the queen was when she heard the name. And when soon afterwards the little man came in, and asked, \"Now, mistress queen, what is my name?\"\n\nAt first she said, \"Is your name Conrad?\"\n\n\"No.\"\n\n\"Is your name Harry?\"\n\n\"No.\"\n\n\"Perhaps your name is Rumpelstiltskin?\"\n\n\"The devil has told you that! The devil has told you that,\" cried the little man, and in his anger he plunged his right foot so deep into the earth that his whole leg went in, and then in rage he pulled at his left leg so hard with both hands that he tore himself in two.</string>
    <string name="story10text">One fine evening a young princess put on her bonnet and clogs, and went out to take a walk by herself in a wood; and when she came to a cool spring of water with a rose in the middle of it, she sat herself down to rest a while. Now she had a golden ball in her hand, which was her favourite plaything; and she was always tossing it up into the air, and catching it again as it fell.\n\nAfter a time she threw it up so high that she missed catching it as it fell; and the ball bounded away, and rolled along on the ground, until at last it fell down into the spring. The princess looked into the spring after her ball, but it was very deep, so deep that she could not see the bottom of it. She began to cry, and said, \'Alas! if I could only get my ball again, I would give all my fine clothes and jewels, and everything that I have in the world.\'\n\nWhilst she was speaking, a frog put its head out of the water, and said, \'Princess, why do you weep so bitterly?\'\n\n\'Alas!\' said she, \'what can you do for me, you nasty frog? My golden ball has fallen into the spring.\'\n\nThe frog said, \'I do not want your pearls, and jewels, and fine clothes; but if you will love me, and let me live with you and eat from off your golden plate, and sleep on your bed, I will bring you your ball again.\'\n\n\'What nonsense,\' thought the princess, \'this silly frog is talking! He can never even get out of the spring to visit me, though he may be able to get my ball for me, and therefore I will tell him he shall have what he asks.\'\n\nSo she said to the frog, \'Well, if you will bring me my ball, I will do all you ask.\'\n\nThen the frog put his head down, and dived deep under the water; and after a little while he came up again, with the ball in his mouth, and threw it on the edge of the spring.\n\nAs soon as the young princess saw her ball, she ran to pick it up; and she was so overjoyed to have it in her hand again, that she never thought of the frog, but ran home with it as fast as she could.\n\nThe frog called after her, \'Stay, princess, and take me with you as you said,\'\n\nBut she did not stop to hear a word.\n\nThe next day, just as the princess had sat down to dinner, she heard a strange noise - tap, tap - plash, plash - as if something was coming up the marble staircase, and soon afterwards there was a gentle knock at the door, and a little voice cried out and said:\n\n\'Open the door, my princess dear,\nOpen the door to thy true love here!\nAnd mind the words that thou and I said\nBy the fountain cool, in the greenwood shade.\'\nThen the princess ran to the door and opened it, and there she saw the frog, whom she had quite forgotten. At this sight she was sadly frightened, and shutting the door as fast as she could came back to her seat.\n\nThe king, her father, seeing that something had frightened her, asked her what was the matter.\n\n\'There is a nasty frog,\' said she, \'at the door, that lifted my ball for me out of the spring this morning. I told him that he should live with me here, thinking that he could never get out of the spring; but there he is at the door, and he wants to come in.\'\n\nWhile she was speaking the frog knocked again at the door, and said:\n\n\'Open the door, my princess dear,\nOpen the door to thy true love here!\nAnd mind the words that thou and I said\nBy the fountain cool, in the greenwood shade.\'\nThen the king said to the young princess, \'As you have given your word you must keep it; so go and let him in.\'\n\nShe did so, and the frog hopped into the room, and then straight on - tap, tap - plash, plash - from the bottom of the room to the top, till he came up close to the table where the princess sat.\n\n\'Pray lift me upon chair,\' said he to the princess, \'and let me sit next to you.\'\n\nAs soon as she had done this, the frog said, \'Put your plate nearer to me, that I may eat out of it.\'\n\nThis she did, and when he had eaten as much as he could, he said, \'Now I am tired; carry me upstairs, and put me into your bed.\' And the princess, though very unwilling, took him up in her hand, and put him upon the pillow of her own bed, where he slept all night long.\n\nAs soon as it was light the frog jumped up, hopped downstairs, and went out of the house.\n\n\'Now, then,\' thought the princess, \'at last he is gone, and I shall be troubled with him no more.\'\n\nBut she was mistaken; for when night came again she heard the same tapping at the door; and the frog came once more, and said:\n\n\'Open the door, my princess dear,\nOpen the door to thy true love here!\nAnd mind the words that thou and I said\nBy the fountain cool, in the greenwood shade.\'\nAnd when the princess opened the door the frog came in, and slept upon her pillow as before, till the morning broke. And the third night he did the same. But when the princess awoke on the following morning she was astonished to see, instead of the frog, a handsome prince, gazing on her with the most beautiful eyes she had ever seen and standing at the head of her bed.\n\nHe told her that he had been enchanted by a spiteful fairy, who had changed him into a frog; and that he had been fated so to abide till some princess should take him out of the spring, and let him eat from her plate, and sleep upon her bed for three nights.\n\n\'You,\' said the prince, \'have broken his cruel charm, and now I have nothing to wish for but that you should go with me into my father\'s kingdom, where I will marry you, and love you as long as you live.\'\n\nThe young princess, you may be sure, was not long in saying \'Yes\' to all this; and as they spoke a brightly coloured coach drove up, with eight beautiful horses, decked with plumes of feathers and a golden harness; and behind the coach rode the prince\'s servant, faithful Heinrich, who had bewailed the misfortunes of his dear master during his enchantment so long and so bitterly, that his heart had well-nigh burst.\n\nThey then took leave of the king, and got into the coach with eight horses, and all set out, full of joy and merriment, for the prince\'s kingdom, which they reached safely; and there they lived happily a great many years.</string>
    <string name="story11text">Of course you know what is meant by a magnifying glass—one of those round spectacle-glasses that make everything look a hundred times bigger than it is? When any one takes one of these and holds it to his eye, and looks at a drop of water from the pond yonder, he sees above a thousand wonderful creatures that are otherwise never discerned in the water. But there they are, and it is no delusion. It almost looks like a great plateful of spiders jumping about in a crowd. And how fierce they are! They tear off each other\'s legs and arms and bodies, before and behind; and yet they are merry and joyful in their way.\n\nNow, there once was an old man whom all the people called Kribble-Krabble, for that was his name. He always wanted the best of everything, and when he could not manage it otherwise, he did it by magic.\n\nThere he sat one day, and held his magnifying-glass to his eye, and looked at a drop of water that had been taken out of a puddle by the ditch. But what a kribbling and krabbling was there! All the thousands of little creatures hopped and sprang and tugged at one another, and ate each other up.\n\n\"That is horrible!\" said old Kribble-Krabble. \"Can one not persuade them to live in peace and quietness, so that each one may mind his own business?\"\n\nAnd he thought it over and over, but it would not do, and so he had recourse to magic.\n\n\"I must give them color, that they may be seen more plainly,\" said he; and he poured something like a little drop of red wine into the drop of water, but it was witches\' blood from the lobes of the ear, the finest kind, at ninepence a drop. And now the wonderful little creatures were pink all over. It looked like a whole town of naked wild men.\n\n\"What have you there?\" asked another old magician, who had no name—and that was the best thing about him.\n\n\"Yes, if you can guess what it is,\" said Kribble-Krabble, \"I\'ll make you a present of it.\"\n\nBut it is not so easy to find out if one does not know.\n\nAnd the magician who had no name looked through the magnifying-glass.\n\nIt looked really like a great town reflected there, in which all the people were running about without clothes. It was terrible! But it was still more terrible to see how one beat and pushed the other, and bit and hacked, and tugged and mauled him. Those at the top were being pulled down, and those at the bottom were struggling upwards.\n\n\"Look! look! his leg is longer than mine! Bah! Away with it! There is one who has a little bruise. It hurts him, but it shall hurt him still more.\"\n\nAnd they hacked away at him, and they pulled at him, and ate him up, because of the little bruise. And there was one sitting as still as any little maiden, and wishing only for peace and quietness. But now she had to come out, and they tugged at her, and pulled her about, and ate her up.\n\n\"That\'s funny!\" said the magician.\n\n\"Yes; but what do you think it is?\" said Kribble-Krabble. \"Can you find that out?\"\n\n\"Why, one can see that easily enough,\" said the other. \"That\'s Paris, or some other great city, for they\'re all alike. It\'s a great city!\"\n\n\"It\'s a drop of puddle water!\" said Kribble-Krabble.</string>
    <string name="story12text">Many, many years ago lived an emperor, who thought so much of new clothes that he spent all his money in order to obtain them; his only ambition was to be always well dressed. He did not care for his soldiers, and the theatre did not amuse him; the only thing, in fact, he thought anything of was to drive out and show a new suit of clothes. He had a coat for every hour of the day; and as one would say of a king \"He is in his cabinet,\" so one could say of him, \"The emperor is in his dressing-room.\"\n\nThe great city where he resided was very gay; every day many strangers from all parts of the globe arrived. One day two swindlers came to this city; they made people believe that they were weavers, and declared they could manufacture the finest cloth to be imagined. Their colours and patterns, they said, were not only exceptionally beautiful, but the clothes made of their material possessed the wonderful quality of being invisible to any man who was unfit for his office or unpardonably stupid.\n\n\"That must be wonderful cloth,\" thought the emperor. \"If I were to be dressed in a suit made of this cloth I should be able to find out which men in my empire were unfit for their places, and I could distinguish the clever from the stupid. I must have this cloth woven for me without delay.\" And he gave a large sum of money to the swindlers, in advance, that they should set to work without any loss of time. They set up two looms, and pretended to be very hard at work, but they did nothing whatever on the looms. They asked for the finest silk and the most precious gold-cloth; all they got they did away with, and worked at the empty looms till late at night.\n\n\"I should very much like to know how they are getting on with the cloth,\" thought the emperor. But he felt rather uneasy when he remembered that he who was not fit for his office could not see it. Personally, he was of opinion that he had nothing to fear, yet he thought it advisable to send somebody else first to see how matters stood. Everybody in the town knew what a remarkable quality the stuff possessed, and all were anxious to see how bad or stupid their neighbours were.\n\n\"I shall send my honest old minister to the weavers,\" thought the emperor. \"He can judge best how the stuff looks, for he is intelligent, and nobody understands his office better than he.\"\n\nThe good old minister went into the room where the swindlers sat before the empty looms. \"Heaven preserve us!\" he thought, and opened his eyes wide, \"I cannot see anything at all,\" but he did not say so. Both swindlers requested him to come near, and asked him if he did not admire the exquisite pattern and the beautiful colours, pointing to the empty looms. The poor old minister tried his very best, but he could see nothing, for there was nothing to be seen. \"Oh dear,\" he thought, \"can I be so stupid? I should never have thought so, and nobody must know it! Is it possible that I am not fit for my office? No, no, I cannot say that I was unable to see the cloth.\"\n\n\"Now, have you got nothing to say?\" said one of the swindlers, while he pretended to be busily weaving.\n\n\"Oh, it is very pretty, exceedingly beautiful,\" replied the old minister looking through his glasses. \"What a beautiful pattern, what brilliant colours! I shall tell the emperor that I like the cloth very much.\"\n\n\"We are pleased to hear that,\" said the two weavers, and described to him the colours and explained the curious pattern. The old minister listened attentively, that he might relate to the emperor what they said; and so he did.\n\nNow the swindlers asked for more money, silk and gold-cloth, which they required for weaving. They kept everything for themselves, and not a thread came near the loom, but they continued, as hitherto, to work at the empty looms.\n\nSoon afterwards the emperor sent another honest courtier to the weavers to see how they were getting on, and if the cloth was nearly finished. Like the old minister, he looked and looked but could see nothing, as there was nothing to be seen.\n\n\"Is it not a beautiful piece of cloth?\" asked the two swindlers, showing and explaining the magnificent pattern, which, however, did not exist.\n\n\"I am not stupid,\" said the man. \"It is therefore my good appointment for which I am not fit. It is very strange, but I must not let any one know it;\" and he praised the cloth, which he did not see, and expressed his joy at the beautiful colours and the fine pattern. \"It is very excellent,\" he said to the emperor.\n\nEverybody in the whole town talked about the precious cloth. At last the emperor wished to see it himself, while it was still on the loom. With a number of courtiers, including the two who had already been there, he went to the two clever swindlers, who now worked as hard as they could, but without using any thread.\n\n\"Is it not magnificent?\" said the two old statesmen who had been there before. \"Your Majesty must admire the colours and the pattern.\" And then they pointed to the empty looms, for they imagined the others could see the cloth.\n\n\"What is this?\" thought the emperor, \"I do not see anything at all. That is terrible! Am I stupid? Am I unfit to be emperor? That would indeed be the most dreadful thing that could happen to me.\"\n\n\"Really,\" he said, turning to the weavers, \"your cloth has our most gracious approval;\" and nodding contentedly he looked at the empty loom, for he did not like to say that he saw nothing. All his attendants, who were with him, looked and looked, and although they could not see anything more than the others, they said, like the emperor, \"It is very beautiful.\" And all advised him to wear the new magnificent clothes at a great procession which was soon to take place. \"It is magnificent, beautiful, excellent,\" one heard them say; everybody seemed to be delighted, and the emperor appointed the two swindlers \"Imperial Court weavers.\"\n\nThe whole night previous to the day on which the procession was to take place, the swindlers pretended to work, and burned more than sixteen candles. People should see that they were busy to finish the emperor\'s new suit. They pretended to take the cloth from the loom, and worked about in the air with big scissors, and sewed with needles without thread, and said at last: \"The emperor\'s new suit is ready now.\"\n\nThe emperor and all his barons then came to the hall; the swindlers held their arms up as if they held something in their hands and said: \"These are the trousers!\" \"This is the coat!\" and \"Here is the cloak!\" and so on. \"They are all as light as a cobweb, and one must feel as if one had nothing at all upon the body; but that is just the beauty of them.\"\n\n\"Indeed!\" said all the courtiers; but they could not see anything, for there was nothing to be seen.\n\n\"Does it please your Majesty now to graciously undress,\" said the swindlers, \"that we may assist your Majesty in putting on the new suit before the large looking-glass?\"\n\nThe emperor undressed, and the swindlers pretended to put the new suit upon him, one piece after another; and the emperor looked at himself in the glass from every side.\n\n\"How well they look! How well they fit!\" said all. \"What a beautiful pattern! What fine colours! That is a magnificent suit of clothes!\"\n\nThe master of the ceremonies announced that the bearers of the canopy, which was to be carried in the procession, were ready.\n\n\"I am ready,\" said the emperor. \"Does not my suit fit me marvellously?\" Then he turned once more to the looking-glass, that people should think he admired his garments.\n\nThe chamberlains, who were to carry the train, stretched their hands to the ground as if they lifted up a train, and pretended to hold something in their hands; they did not like people to know that they could not see anything.\n\nThe emperor marched in the procession under the beautiful canopy, and all who saw him in the street and out of the windows exclaimed: \"Indeed, the emperor\'s new suit is incomparable! What a long train he has! How well it fits him!\" Nobody wished to let others know he saw nothing, for then he would have been unfit for his office or too stupid. Never emperor\'s clothes were more admired.\n\n\"But he has nothing on at all,\" said a little child at last. \"Good heavens! listen to the voice of an innocent child,\" said the father, and one whispered to the other what the child had said. \"But he has nothing on at all,\" cried at last the whole people. That made a deep impression upon the emperor, for it seemed to him that they were right; but he thought to himself, \"Now I must bear up to the end.\" And the chamberlains walked with still greater dignity, as if they carried the train which did not exist.</string>
    <string name="story13text">The Flea, the Grasshopper, and the Skipjack once wanted to see which of them could jump highest; and they invited the whole world, and whoever else would come, to see the grand sight. And there the three famous jumpers were met together in the room.\n\n\"Yes, I\'ll give my daughter to him who jumps highest,\" said the King, \"for it would be mean to let these people jump for nothing.\"\n\nThe Flea stepped out first. He had very pretty manners, and bowed in all directions, for he had young ladies\' blood in his veins, and was accustomed to consort only with human beings; and that was of great consequence.\n\nThen came the Grasshopper: he was certainly much heavier, but he had a good figure, and wore the green uniform that was born with him. This person, moreover, maintained that he belonged to a very old family in the land of Egypt, and that he was highly esteemed there. He had just come from the field, he said, and had been put into a card house three stories high, and all made of picture cards with the figures turned inwards. There were doors and windows in the house, cut in the body of the Queen of Hearts.\n\n\"I sing so,\" he said, \"that sixteen native crickets who have chirped from their youth up, and have never yet had a card house of their own, would become thinner than they are with envy if they were to hear me.\"\n\nBoth of them, the Flea and the Grasshopper, took care to announce who they were, and that they considered themselves entitled to marry a Princess.\n\nThe Skipjack said nothing, but it was said of him that he thought all the more; and directly the Yard Dog had smelt at him he was ready to assert that the Skipjack was of good family, and formed from the breastbone of an undoubted goose. The old councillor, who had received three medals for holding his tongue, declared that the Skipjack possessed the gift of prophecy; one could tell by his bones whether there would be a severe winter or a mild one; and that\'s more than one can always tell from the breastbone of the man who writes the almanac.\n\n\"I shall not say anything more,\" said the old King. \"I only go on quietly, and always think the best.\"\n\nNow they were to take their jump. The Flea sprang so high that no one could see him; and then they asserted that he had not jumped at all. That was very mean. The Grasshopper only sprang half as high, but he sprang straight into the King\'s face, and the King declared that was horribly rude. The Skipjack stood a long time considering; at last people thought that he could not jump at all.\n\n\"I only hope he\'s not become unwell,\" said the Yard Dog, and then he smelt at him again.\n\n\"Tap!\" he sprang with a little crooked jump just into the lap of the Princess, who sat on a low golden stool.\n\nThen the King said, \"The highest leap was taken by him who jumped up to my daughter; for therein lies the point; but it requires head to achieve that, and the Skipjack has shown that he has a head.\"\n\nAnd so he had the Princess.\n\n\"I jumped highest, after all,\" said the Flea. \"But it\'s all the same. Let her have the goose-bone with its lump of wax and bit of stick. I jumped to the highest; but in this world a body is required if one wishes to be seen.\"\n\nAnd the Flea went into foreign military service, where it is said he was killed.\n\nThe Grasshopper seated himself out in the ditch, and thought and considered how things happened in the world. And he too said, \"Body is required! body is required!\" And then he sang his own melancholy song, and from that we have gathered this story, which they say is not true, though it\'s in print.</string>
    <string name="story14text">In a nursery where a number of toys lay scattered about, a money-box stood on the top of a very high wardrobe. It was made of clay in the shape of a pig, and had been bought of the potter. In the back of the pig was a slit, and this slit had been enlarged with a knife, so that dollars, or crown pieces, might slip through; and, indeed there were two in the box, besides a number of pence. The money-pig was stuffed so full that it could no longer rattle, which is the highest state of perfection to which a money-pig can attain. There he stood upon the cupboard, high and lofty, looking down upon everything else in the room. He knew very well that he had enough inside him to buy up all the other toys, and this gave him a very good opinion of his own value. The rest thought of this fact also, although they did not express it, for there were so many other things to talk about. A large doll, still handsome, though rather old, for her neck had been mended, lay inside one of the drawers which was partly open. She called out to the others, \"Let us have a game at being men and women, that is something worth playing at.\"\n\nUpon this there was a great uproar; even the engravings, which hung in frames on the wall, turned round in their excitement, and showed that they had a wrong side to them, although they had not the least intention to expose themselves in this way, or to object to the game. It was late at night, but as the moon shone through the windows, they had light at a cheap rate. And as the game was now to begin, all were invited to take part in it, even the children\'s wagon, which certainly belonged to the coarser playthings. \"Each has its own value,\" said the wagon; \"we cannot all be noblemen; there must be some to do the work.\"\n\nThe money-pig was the only one who received a written invitation. He stood so high that they were afraid he would not accept a verbal message. But in his reply, he said, if he had to take a part, he must enjoy the sport from his own home; they were to arrange for him to do so; and so they did. The little toy theatre was therefore put up in such a way that the money-pig could look directly into it. Some wanted to begin with a comedy, and afterwards to have a tea party and a discussion for mental improvement, but they commenced with the latter first. The rocking-horse spoke of training and races; the wagon of railways and steam power, for these subjects belonged to each of their professions, and it was right they should talk of them. The clock talked politics—\"tick, tick;\" he professed to know what was the time of day, but there was a whisper that he did not go correctly. The bamboo cane stood by, looking stiff and proud: he was vain of his brass ferrule and silver top, and on the sofa lay two worked cushions, pretty but stupid. When the play at the little theatre began, the rest sat and looked on; they were requested to applaud and stamp, or crack, when they felt gratified with what they saw. But the riding-whip said he never cracked for old people, only for the young who were not yet married. \"I crack for everybody,\" said the cracker.\n\n\"Yes, and a fine noise you make,\" thought the audience, as the play went on.\n\nIt was not worth much, but it was very well played, and all the characters turned their painted sides to the audience, for they were made only to be seen on one side. The acting was wonderful, excepting that sometimes they came out beyond the lamps, because the wires were a little too long. The doll, whose neck had been darned, was so excited that the place in her neck burst, and the money-pig declared he must do something for one of the players, as they had all pleased him so much. So he made up his mind to remember one of them in his will, as the one to be buried with him in the family vault, whenever that event should happen. They all enjoyed the comedy so much, that they gave up all thoughts of the tea party, and only carried out their idea of intellectual amusement, which they called playing at men and women; and there was nothing wrong about it, for it was only play. All the while, each one thought most of himself, or of what the money-pig could be thinking. His thoughts were on, as he supposed, a very distant time—of making his will, and of his burial, and of when it might all come to pass. Certainly sooner than he expected—for all at once down he came from the top of the press, fell on the ground, and was broken to pieces. Then the pennies hopped and danced about in the most amusing manner. The little ones twirled round like tops, and the large ones rolled away as far as they could, especially the one great silver crown piece who had often to go out into the world, and now he had his wish as well as all the rest of the money. The pieces of the money-pig were thrown into the dust-bin, and the next day there stood a new money-pig on the cupboard, but it had not a farthing in its inside yet, and therefore, like the old one, it could not rattle. This was the beginning with him, and we will make it the end of our story.</string>
    <string name="story15text">Once upon a time there was a prince who wanted to marry a princess; but she would have to be a real princess. He travelled all over the world to find one, but nowhere could he get what he wanted. There were princesses enough, but it was difficult to find out whether they were real ones. There was always something about them that was not as it should be. So he came home again and was sad, for he would have liked very much to have a real princess.\n\nOne evening a terrible storm came on; there was thunder and lightning, and the rain poured down in torrents. Suddenly a knocking was heard at the city gate, and the old king went to open it.\n\nIt was a princess standing out there in front of the gate. But, good gracious! what a sight the rain and the wind had made her look. The water ran down from her hair and clothes; it ran down into the toes of her shoes and out again at the heels. And yet she said that she was a real princess.\n\nWell, we\'ll soon find that out, thought the old queen. But she said nothing, went into the bed-room, took all the bedding off the bedstead, and laid a pea on the bottom; then she took twenty mattresses and laid them on the pea, and then twenty eider-down beds on top of the mattresses.\n\nOn this the princess had to lie all night. In the morning she was asked how she had slept.\n\n\"Oh, very badly!\" said she. \"I have scarcely closed my eyes all night. Heaven only knows what was in the bed, but I was lying on something hard, so that I am black and blue all over my body. It\'s horrible!\"\n\nNow they knew that she was a real princess because she had felt the pea right through the twenty mattresses and the twenty eider-down beds.\n\nNobody but a real princess could be as sensitive as that.\n\nSo the prince took her for his wife, for now he knew that he had a real princess; and the pea was put in the museum, where it may still be seen, if no one has stolen it.\n\nThere, that is a true story.</string>
    <string name="story16text">There was once a shilling, which came forth from the mint springing and shouting, \"Hurrah! now I am going out into the wide world.\" And truly it did go out into the wide world. The children held it with warm hands, the miser with a cold and convulsive grasp, and the old people turned it about, goodness knows how many times, while the young people soon allowed it to roll away from them. The shilling was made of silver, it contained very little copper, and considered itself quite out in the world when it had been circulated for a year in the country in which it had been coined. One day, it really did go out into the world, for it belonged to a gentleman who was about to travel in foreign lands. This gentleman was not aware that the shilling lay at the bottom of his purse when he started, till he one day found it between his fingers. \"Why,\" cried he, \"here is a shilling from home; well, it must go on its travels with me now!\" and the shilling jumped and rattled for joy, when it was put back again into the purse.\n\nHere it lay among a number of foreign companions, who were always coming and going, one taking the place of another, but the shilling from home was always put back, and had to remain in the purse, which was certainly a mark of distinction. Many weeks passed, during which the shilling had travelled a long distance in the purse, without in the least knowing where he was. He had found out that the other coins were French and Italian; and one coin said they were in this town, and another said they were in that, but the shilling was unable to make out or imagine what they meant. A man certainly cannot see much of the world if he is tied up in a bag, and this was really the shilling\'s fate. But one day, as he was lying in the purse, he noticed that it was not quite closed, and so he slipped near to the opening to have a little peep into society. He certainly had not the least idea of what would follow, but he was curious, and curiosity often brings its own punishment. In his eagerness, he came so near the edge of the purse that he slipped out into the pocket of the trousers; and when, in the evening, the purse was taken out, the shilling was left behind in the corner to which it had fallen. As the clothes were being carried into the hall, the shilling fell out on the floor, unheard and unnoticed by any one. The next morning the clothes were taken back to the room, the gentleman put them on, and started on his journey again; but the shilling remained behind on the floor. After a time it was found, and being considered a good coin, was placed with three other coins. \"Ah,\" thought the shilling, \"this is pleasant; I shall now see the world, become acquainted with other people, and learn other customs.\"\n\n\"Do you call that a shilling?\" said some one the next moment. \"That is not a genuine coin of the country,—it is false; it is good for nothing.\"\n\nNow begins the story as it was afterwards related by the shilling himself.\n\n\"\'False! good for nothing!\' said he. That remark went through and through me like a dagger. I knew that I had a true ring, and that mine was a genuine stamp. These people must at all events be wrong, or they could not mean me. But yes, I was the one they called \'false, and good for nothing.\'\n\n\"\'Then I must pay it away in the dark,\' said the man who had received me. So I was to be got rid of in the darkness, and be again insulted in broad daylight.\n\n\"\'False! good for nothing!\' Oh, I must contrive to get lost, thought I. And I trembled between the fingers of the people every time they tried to pass me off slyly as a coin of the country. Ah! unhappy shilling that I was! Of what use were my silver, my stamp, and my real value here, where all these qualities were worthless. In the eyes of the world, a man is valued just according to the opinion formed of him. It must be a shocking thing to have a guilty conscience, and to be sneaking about on account of wicked deeds. As for me, innocent as I was, I could not help shuddering before their eyes whenever they brought me out, for I knew I should be thrown back again up the table as a false pretender. At length I was paid away to a poor old woman, who received me as wages for a hard day\'s work. But she could not again get rid of me; no one would take me. I was to the woman a most unlucky shilling. \'I am positively obliged to pass this shilling to somebody,\' said she; \'I cannot, with the best intentions, lay by a bad shilling. The rich baker shall have it,—he can bear the loss better than I can. But, after all, it is not a right thing to do.\'\n\n\"\'Ah!\' sighed I to myself, \'am I also to be a burden on the conscience of this poor woman? Am I then in my old days so completely changed?\' The woman offered me to the rich baker, but he knew the current money too well, and as soon as he received me he threw me almost in the woman\'s face. She could get no bread for me, and I felt quite grieved to the heart that I should be cause of so much trouble to another, and be treated as a cast-off coin. I who, in my young days, felt so joyful in the certainty of my own value, and knew so well that I bore a genuine stamp. I was as sorrowful now as a poor shilling can be when nobody will have him. The woman took me home again with her, and looking at me very earnestly, she said, \'No, I will not try to deceive any one with thee again. I will bore a hole through thee, that everyone may know that thou art a false and worthless thing; and yet, why should I do that? Very likely thou art a lucky shilling. A thought has just struck me that it is so, and I believe it. Yes, I will make a hole in the shilling,\' said she, \'and run a string through it, and then give it to my neighbor\'s little one to hang round her neck, as a lucky shilling.\' So she drilled a hole through me.\n\n\"It is really not at all pleasant to have a hole bored through one, but we can submit to a great deal when it is done with a good intention. A string was drawn through the hole, and I became a kind of medal. They hung me round the neck of a little child, and the child laughed at me and kissed me, and I rested for one whole night on the warm, innocent breast of a child.\n\n\"In the morning the child\'s mother took me between her fingers, and had certain thoughts about me, which I very soon found out. First, she looked for a pair of scissors, and cut the string.\n\n\"\'Lucky shilling!\' said she, \'certainly this is what I mean to try.\' Then she laid me in vinegar till I became quite green, and after that she filled up the hole with cement, rubbed me a little to brighten me up, and went out in the twilight hour to the lottery collector, to buy herself a ticket, with a shilling that should bring luck. How everything seemed to cause me trouble. The lottery collector pressed me so hard that I thought I should crack. I had been called false, I had been thrown away,—that I knew; and there were many shillings and coins with inscriptions and stamps of all kinds lying about. I well knew how proud they were, so I avoided them from very shame. With the collector were several men who seemed to have a great deal to do, so I fell unnoticed into a chest, among several other coins.\n\n\"Whether the lottery ticket gained a prize, I know not; but this I know, that in a very few days after, I was recognized as a bad shilling, and laid aside. Everything that happened seemed always to add to my sorrow. Even if a man has a good character, it is of no use for him to deny what is said of him, for he is not considered an impartial judge of himself.\n\n\"A year passed, and in this way I had been changed from hand to hand; always abused, always looked at with displeasure, and trusted by no one; but I trusted in myself, and had no confidence in the world. Yes, that was a very dark time.\n\n\"At length one day I was passed to a traveller, a foreigner, the very same who had brought me away from home; and he was simple and true-hearted enough to take me for current coin. But would he also attempt to pass me? and should I again hear the outcry, \'False! good-for-nothing!\' The traveller examined me attentively, \'I took thee for good coin,\' said he; then suddenly a smile spread all over his face. I have never seen such a smile on any other face as on his. \'Now this is singular,\' said he, \'it is a coin from my own country; a good, true, shilling from home. Some one has bored a hole through it, and people have no doubt called it false. How curious that it should come into my hands. I will take it home with me to my own house.\'\n\n\"Joy thrilled through me when I heard this. I had been once more called a good, honest shilling, and I was to go back to my own home, where each and all would recognize me, and know that I was made of good silver, and bore a true, genuine stamp. I should have been glad in my joy to throw out sparks of fire, but it has never at any time been my nature to sparkle. Steel can do so, but not silver. I was wrapped up in fine, white paper, that I might not mix with the other coins and be lost; and on special occasions, when people from my own country happened to be present, I was brought forward and spoken of very kindly. They said I was very interesting, and it was really quite worth while to notice that those who are interesting have often not a single word to say for themselves.\n\n\"At length I reached home. All my cares were at an end. Joy again overwhelmed me; for was I not good silver, and had I not a genuine stamp? I had no more insults or disappointments to endure; although, indeed, there was a hole through me, as if I were false; but suspicions are nothing when a man is really true, and every one should persevere in acting honestly, for an will be made right in time. That is my firm belief,\" said the shilling.</string>
    <string name="story17text">On one of the Danish islands, where old Thingstones, the seats of justice of our forefathers, still stand in the cornfields, and huge trees rise in the forests of beech, there lies a little town whose low houses are covered with red tiles. In one of these houses strange things were brewing over the glowing coals on the open hearth; there was a boiling going on in glasses, and a mixing and distilling, while herbs were being cut up and pounded in mortars. An elderly man looked after it all.\n\n\"One must only do the right thing,\" he said; \"yes, the right—the correct thing. One must find out the truth concerning every created particle, and keep to that.\"\n\nIn the room with the good housewife sat her two sons; they were still small, but had great thoughts. Their mother, too, had always spoken to them of right and justice, and exhorted them to keep to the truth, which she said was the countenance of the Lord in this world.\n\nThe elder of the boys looked roguish and enterprising. He took a delight in reading of the forces of nature, of the sun and the moon; no fairy tale pleased him so much. Oh, how beautiful it must be, he thought, to go on voyages of discovery, or to find out how to imitate the wings of birds and then to be able to fly! Yes, to find that out was the right thing. Father was right, and mother was right—truth holds the world together.\n\nThe younger brother was quieter, and buried himself entirely in his books. When he read about Jacob dressing himself in sheep-skins to personify Esau, and so to usurp his brother\'s birthright, he would clench his little fist in anger against the deceiver; when he read of tyrants and of the injustice and wickedness of the world, tears would come into his eyes, and he was quite filled with the thought of the justice and truth which must and would triumph.\n\nOne evening he was lying in bed, but the curtains were not yet drawn close, and the light streamed in upon him; he had taken his book into bed with him, for he wanted to finish reading the story of Solon. His thoughts lifted and carried him away a wonderful distance; it seemed to him as if the bed had become a ship flying along under full sail. Was he dreaming, or what was happening? It glided over the rolling waves and across the ocean of time, and to him came the voice of Solon; spoken in a strange tongue, yet intelligible to him, he heard the Danish motto: \"By law the land is ruled.\"\n\nThe genius of the human race stood in the humble room, bent down over the bed and imprinted a kiss on the boy\'s forehead: \"Be thou strong in fame and strong in the battle of life! With truth in thy heart fly toward the land of truth!\"\n\nThe elder brother was not yet in bed; he was standing at the window looking out at the mist which rose from the meadows. They were not elves dancing out there, as their old nurse had told him; he knew better—they were vapours which were warmer than the air, and that is why they rose. A shooting star lit up the sky, and the boy\'s thoughts passed in a second from the vapours of the earth up to the shining meteor. The stars gleamed in the heavens, and it seemed as if long golden threads hung down from them to the earth.\n\n\"Fly with me,\" sang a voice, which the boy heard in his heart. And the mighty genius of mankind, swifter than a bird and than an arrow—swifter than anything of earthly origin—carried him out into space, where the heavenly bodies are bound together by the rays that pass from star to star. Our earth revolved in the thin air, and the cities upon it seemed to lie close to each other. Through the spheres echoed the words:\n\n\"What is near, what is far, when thou art lifted by the mighty genius of mind?\"\n\nAnd again the boy stood by the window, gazing out, whilst his younger brother lay in bed. Their mother called them by their names: \"Anders Sandoe\" and \"Hans Christian.\"\n\nDenmark and the whole world knows them—the two brothers Oersted.</string>
    <string name="story18text">An Ox came down to a reedy pool to drink. As he splashed heavily into the water, he crushed a young Frog into the mud.\n\nThe old Frog soon missed the little one and asked his brothers and sisters what had become of him.\n\n\"A great big monster,\" said one of them, \"stepped on little brother with one of his huge feet!\"\n\n\"Big, was he!\" said the old Frog, puffing herself up. \"Was he as big as this?\"\n\n\"Oh, much bigger!\" they cried.\n\nThe Frog puffed up still more.\n\n\n\"He could not have been bigger than this,\" she said. But the little Frogs all declared that the monster was much, much bigger and the old Frog kept puffing herself out more and more until, all at once, she burst.\n\nMoral: Do not attempt the impossible.</string>
    <string name="story19text">The Mice once called a meeting to decide on a plan to free themselves of their enemy, the Cat. At least they wished to find some way of knowing when she was coming, so they might have time to run away. Indeed, something had to be done, for they lived in such constant fear of her claws that they hardly dared stir from their dens by night or day.\n\nMany plans were discussed, but none of them was thought good enough. At last a very young Mouse got up and said:\n\n\"I have a plan that seems very simple, but I know it will be successful.\n\nAll we have to do is to hang a bell about the Cat\'s neck. When we hear the bell ringing we will know immediately that our enemy is coming.\"\n\nAll the Mice were much surprised that they had not thought of such a plan before. But in the midst of the rejoicing over their good fortune, an old Mouse arose and said:\n\n\"I will say that the plan of the young Mouse is very good. But let me ask one question: Who will bell the Cat?\"\n\nMoral: It is one thing to say that something should be done, but quite a different matter to do it.</string>
    <string name="story20text">A Town Mouse once visited a relative who lived in the country. For lunch the Country Mouse served wheat stalks, roots, and acorns, with a dash of cold water for drink. The Town Mouse ate very sparingly, nibbling a little of this and a little of that, and by her manner making it very plain that she ate the simple food only to be polite.\n\nAfter the meal the friends had a long talk, or rather the Town Mouse talked about her life in the city while the Country Mouse listened. They then went to bed in a cozy nest in the hedgerow and slept in quiet and comfort until morning. In her sleep the Country Mouse dreamed she was a Town Mouse with all the luxuries and delights of city life that her friend had described for her. So the next day when the Town Mouse asked the Country Mouse to go home with her to the city, she gladly said yes.\n\nWhen they reached the mansion in which the Town Mouse lived, they found on the table in the dining room the leavings of a very fine banquet. There were sweetmeats and jellies, pastries, delicious cheeses, indeed, the most tempting foods that a Mouse can imagine. But just as the Country Mouse was about to nibble a dainty bit of pastry, she heard a Cat mew loudly and scratch at the door. In great fear the Mice scurried to a hiding place, where they lay quite still for a long time, hardly daring to breathe. When at last they ventured back to the feast, the door opened suddenly and in came the servants to clear the table, followed by the House Dog.\n\n\nThe Country Mouse stopped in the Town Mouse\'s den only long enough to pick up her carpet bag and umbrella.\n\n\"You may have luxuries and dainties that I have not,\" she said as she hurried away, \"but I prefer my plain food and simple life in the country with the peace and security that go with it.\"\n\nMoral: Poverty with security is better than plenty in the midst of fear and uncertainty.</string>
    <string name="story21text">A Fox one day spied a beautiful bunch of ripe grapes hanging from a vine trained along the branches of a tree. The grapes seemed ready to burst with juice, and the Fox\'s mouth watered as he gazed longingly at them.\n\nThe bunch hung from a high branch, and the Fox had to jump for it. The first time he jumped he missed it by a long way. So he walked off a short distance and took a running leap at it, only to fall short once more. Again and again he tried, but in vain.\n\nNow he sat down and looked at the grapes in disgust.\n\n\"What a fool I am,\" he said. \"Here I am wearing myself out to get a bunch of sour grapes that are not worth gaping for.\"\n\nAnd off he walked very, very scornfully.\n\nMoral: There are many who pretend to despise and belittle that which is beyond their reach.</string>
    <string name="story22text">A Wolf had been feasting too greedily, and a bone had stuck crosswise in his throat. He could get it neither up nor down, and of course he could not eat a thing. Naturally that was an awful state of affairs for a greedy Wolf.\n\nSo away he hurried to the Crane. He was sure that she, with her long neck and bill, would easily be able to reach the bone and pull it out.\n\n\"I will reward you very handsomely,\" said the Wolf, \"if you pull that bone out for me.\"\n\nThe Crane, as you can imagine, was very uneasy about putting her head in a Wolf\'s throat. But she was grasping in nature, so she did what the Wolf asked her to do.\n\nWhen the Wolf felt that the bone was gone, he started to walk away.\n\n\"But what about my reward!\" called the Crane anxiously.\n\n\"What!\" snarled the Wolf, whirling around. \"Haven\'t you got it? Isn\'t it enough that I let you take your head out of my mouth without snapping it off?\"\n\nMoral: Expect no reward for serving the wicked.</string>
    <string name="story23text">A Gnat flew over the meadow with much buzzing for so small a creature and settled on the tip of one of the horns of a Bull. After he had rested a short time, he made ready to fly away. But before he left he begged the Bull\'s pardon for having used his horn for a resting place.\n\n\"You must be very glad to have me go now,\" he said.\n\n\"It\'s all the same to me,\" replied the Bull. \"I did not even know you were there.\"\n\nMoral: We are often of greater importance in our own eyes than in the eyes of our neighbor. The smaller the mind the greater the conceit.</string>
    <string name="story24text">Two Travellers, walking in the noonday sun, sought the shade of a widespreading tree to rest. As they lay looking up among the pleasant leaves, they saw that it was a Plane Tree.\n\n\"How useless is the Plane!\" said one of them. \"It bears no fruit whatever, and only serves to litter the ground with leaves.\"\n\n\"Ungrateful creatures!\" said a voice from the Plane Tree. \"You lie here in my cooling shade, and yet you say I am useless! Thus ungratefully, O Jupiter, do men receive their blessings!\"\n\nMoral: Our best blessings are often the least appreciated.</string>
    <string name="story25text">The Owl always takes her sleep during the day. Then after sundown, when the rosy light fades from the sky and the shadows rise slowly through the wood, out she comes ruffling and blinking from the old hollow tree. Now her weird \"hoo-hoo-hoo-oo-oo\" echoes through the quiet wood, and she begins her hunt for the bugs and beetles, frogs and mice she likes so well to eat.\n\nNow there was a certain old Owl who had become very cross and hard to please as she grew older, especially if anything disturbed her daily slumbers. One warm summer afternoon as she dozed away in her den in the old oak tree, a Grasshopper nearby began a joyous but very raspy song. Out popped the old Owl\'s head from the opening in the tree that served her both for door and for window.\n\n\"Get away from here, sir,\" she said to the Grasshopper. \"Have you no manners? You should at least respect my age and leave me to sleep in quiet!\"\n\nBut the Grasshopper answered saucily that he had as much right to his place in the sun as the Owl had to her place in the old oak. Then he struck up a louder and still more rasping tune.\n\nThe wise old Owl knew quite well that it would do no good to argue with the Grasshopper, nor with anybody else for that matter. Besides, her eyes were not sharp enough by day to permit her to punish the Grasshopper as he deserved. So she laid aside all hard words and spoke very kindly to him.\n\n\"Well sir,\" she said, \"if I must stay awake, I am going to settle right down to enjoy your singing. Now that I think of it, I have a wonderful wine here, sent me from Olympus, of which I am told Apollo drinks before he sings to the high gods. Please come up and taste this delicious drink with me. I know it will make you sing like Apollo himself.\"\n\n\nThe foolish Grasshopper was taken in by the Owl\'s flattering words. Up he jumped to the Owl\'s den, but as soon as he was near enough so the old Owl could see him clearly, she pounced upon him and ate him up.\n\nMoral: Flattery is not a proof of true admiration. Do not let flattery throw you off your guard against an enemy.</string>
    <string name="story26text">A Giant Oak stood near a brook in which grew some slender Reeds. When the wind blew, the great Oak stood proudly upright with its hundred arms uplifted to the sky. But the Reeds bowed low in the wind and sang a sad and mournful song.\n\n\"You have reason to complain,\" said the Oak. \"The slightest breeze that ruffles the surface of the water makes you bow your heads, while I, the mighty Oak, stand upright and firm before the howling tempest.\"\n\n\"Do not worry about us,\" replied the Reeds. \"The winds do not harm us. We bow before them and so we do not break. You, in all your pride and strength, have so far resisted their blows. But the end is coming.\"\n\nAs the Reeds spoke a great hurricane rushed out of the north. The Oak stood proudly and fought against the storm, while the yielding Reeds bowed low. The wind redoubled in fury, and all at once the great tree fell, torn up by the roots, and lay among the pitying Reeds.\n\nMoral: Better to yield when it is folly to resist, than to resist stubbornly and be destroyed.</string>
    <string name="story27text">In a spell of dry weather, when the Birds could find very little to drink, a thirsty Crow found a pitcher with a little water in it. But the pitcher was high and had a narrow neck, and no matter how he tried, the Crow could not reach the water. The poor thing felt as if he must die of thirst.\n\nThen an idea came to him. Picking up some small pebbles, he dropped them into the pitcher one by one. With each pebble the water rose a little higher until at last it was near enough so he could drink.\n\nMoral: In a pinch a good use of our wits may help us out.</string>
    <string name="story28text">Two Goats, frisking gayly on the rocky steeps of a mountain valley, chanced to meet, one on each side of a deep chasm through which poured a mighty mountain torrent. The trunk of a fallen tree formed the only means of crossing the chasm, and on this not even two squirrels could have passed each other in safety. The narrow path would have made the bravest tremble. Not so our Goats. Their pride would not permit either to stand aside for the other.\n\nOne set her foot on the log. The other did likewise. In the middle they met horn to horn. Neither would give way, and so they both fell, to be swept away by the roaring torrent below.\n\nMoral: It is better to yield than to come to misfortune through stubbornness.</string>
    <string name="story29text">A Wild Boar was sharpening his tusks busily against the stump of a tree, when a Fox happened by. Now the Fox was always looking for a chance to make fun of his neighbors. So he made a great show of looking anxiously about, as if in fear of some hidden enemy. But the Boar kept right on with his work.\n\n\"Why are you doing that?\" asked the Fox at last with a grin. \"There isn\'t any danger that I can see.\"\n\n\"True enough,\" replied the Boar, \"but when danger does come there will not be time for such work as this. My weapons will have to be ready for use then, or I shall suffer for it.\"\n\nMoral: Preparedness for war is the best guarantee of peace.</string>
    <string name="story30text">A Heron was walking sedately along the bank of a stream, his eyes on the clear water, and his long neck and pointed bill ready to snap up a likely morsel for his breakfast. The clear water swarmed with fish, but Master Heron was hard to please that morning.\n\n\"No small fry for me,\" he said. \"Such scanty fare is not fit for a Heron.\"\n\nNow a fine young Perch swam near.\n\n\"No indeed,\" said the Heron. \"I wouldn\'t even trouble to open my beak for anything like that!\"\n\nAs the sun rose, the fish left the shallow water near the shore and swam below into the cool depths toward the middle. The Heron saw no more fish, and very glad was he at last to breakfast on a tiny Snail.\n\nMoral: Do not be too hard to suit or you may have to be content with the worst or with nothing at all.</string>
    <string name="story31text">The Fox one day thought of a plan to amuse himself at the expense of the Stork, at whose odd appearance he was always laughing.\n\n\"You must come and dine with me today,\" he said to the Stork, smiling to himself at the trick he was going to play. The Stork gladly accepted the invitation and arrived in good time and with a very good appetite.\n\nFor dinner the Fox served soup. But it was set out in a very shallow dish, and all the Stork could do was to wet the very tip of his bill. Not a drop of soup could he get. But the Fox lapped it up easily, and, to increase the disappointment of the Stork, made a great show of enjoyment.\n\nThe hungry Stork was much displeased at the trick, but he was a calm, even-tempered fellow and saw no good in flying into a rage. Instead, not long afterward, he invited the Fox to dine with him in turn. The Fox arrived promptly at the time that had been set, and the Stork served a fish dinner that had a very appetizing smell. But it was served in a tall jar with a very narrow neck. The Stork could easily get at the food with his long bill, but all the Fox could do was to lick the outside of the jar, and sniff at the delicious odor. And when the Fox lost his temper, the Stork said calmly:\n\n\"Do not play tricks on your neighbors unless you can stand the same treatment yourself.\"</string>
    <string name="story32text">A Stag, drinking from a crystal spring, saw himself mirrored in the clear water. He greatly admired the graceful arch of his antlers, but he was very much ashamed of his spindling legs.\n\n\"How can it be,\" he sighed, \"that I should be cursed with such legs when I have so magnificent a crown.\"\n\nAt that moment he scented a panther and in an instant was bounding away through the forest. But as he ran his wide-spreading antlers caught in the branches of the trees, and soon the Panther overtook him. Then the Stag perceived that the legs of which he was so ashamed would have saved him had it not been for the useless ornaments on his head.\n\nWe often make much of the ornamental and despise the useful.</string>
    <string name="story33text">One bright evening as the sun was sinking on a glorious world a wise old Cock flew into a tree to roost. Before he composed himself to rest, he flapped his wings three times and crowed loudly. But just as he was about to put his head under his wing, his beady eyes caught a flash of red and a glimpse of a long pointed nose, and there just below him stood Master Fox.\n\n\"Have you heard the wonderful news?\" cried the Fox in a very joyful and excited manner.\n\n\"What news?\" asked the Cock very calmly. But he had a queer, fluttery feeling inside him, for, you know, he was very much afraid of the Fox.\n\n\"Your family and mine and all other animals have agreed to forget their differences and live in peace and friendship from now on forever. Just think of it! I simply cannot wait to embrace you! Do come down, dear friend, and let us celebrate the joyful event.\"\n\n\"How grand!\" said the Cock. \"I certainly am delighted at the news.\" But he spoke in an absent way, and stretching up on tiptoes, seemed to be looking at something afar off.\n\n\"What is it you see?\" asked the Fox a little anxiously.\n\n\"Why, it looks to me like a couple of Dogs coming this way. They must have heard the good news and—\"\n\nBut the Fox did not wait to hear more. Off he started on a run.\n\n\"Wait,\" cried the Cock. \"Why do you run? The Dogs are friends of yours now!\"\n\n\"Yes,\" answered the Fox. \"But they might not have heard the news. Besides, I have a very important errand that I had almost forgotten about.\"\n\nThe Cock smiled as he buried his head in his feathers and went to sleep, for he had succeeded in outwitting a very crafty enemy.\n\nMoral: The trickster is easily tricked.</string>
    <string name="story34text">A Fox fell into a well, and though it was not very deep, he found that he could not get out again. After he had been in the well a long time, a thirsty Goat came by. The Goat thought the Fox had gone down to drink, and so he asked if the water was good.\n\n\"The finest in the whole country,\" said the crafty Fox, \"jump in and try it. There is more than enough for both of us.\"\n\nThe thirsty Goat immediately jumped in and began to drink. The Fox just as quickly jumped on the Goat\'s back and leaped from the tip of the Goat\'s horns out of the well\n\nThe foolish Goat now saw what a plight he had got into, and begged the Fox to help him out. But the Fox was already on his way to the woods\n\n\"If you had as much sense as you have beard, old fellow,\" he said as he ran, \"you would have been more cautious about finding a way to get out again before you jumped in.\"\n\nMoral: Look before you leap.</string>
    <string name="story35text">A Fox and a Leopard, resting lazily after a generous dinner, amused themselves by disputing about their good looks. The Leopard was very proud of his glossy, spotted coat and made disdainful remarks about the Fox, whose appearance he declared was quite ordinary.\n\nThe Fox prided himself on his fine bushy tail with its tip of white, but he was wise enough to see that he could not rival the Leopard in looks. Still he kept up a flow of sarcastic talk, just to exercise his wits and to have the fun of disputing. The Leopard was about to lose his temper when the Fox got up, yawning lazily.\n\n\"You may have a very smart coat,\" he said, \"but you would be a great deal better off if you had a little more smartness inside your head and less on your ribs, the way I am. That\'s what I call real beauty.\"\n\nMoral: A fine coat is not always an indication of an attractive mind.</string>
    <string name="story36text">A young Mouse in search of adventure was running along the bank of a pond where lived a Frog. When the Frog saw the Mouse, he swam to the bank and croaked:\n\n\"Won\'t you pay me a visit? I can promise you a good time if you do.\"\n\nThe Mouse did not need much coaxing, for he was very anxious to see the world and everything in it. But though he could swim a little, he did not dare risk going into the pond without some help.\n\nThe Frog had a plan. He tied the Mouse\'s leg to his own with a tough reed. Then into the pond he jumped, dragging his foolish companion with him. The Mouse soon had enough of it and wanted to return to shore; but the treacherous Frog had other plans. He pulled the Mouse down under the water and drowned him. But before he could untie the reed that bound him to the dead Mouse, a Hawk came sailing over the pond. Seeing the body of the Mouse floating on the water, the Hawk swooped down, seized the Mouse and carried it off, with the Frog dangling from its leg. Thus at one swoop he had caught both meat and fish for his dinner.\n\nMoral: Those who seek to harm others often come to harm themselves through their own deceit.</string>
    <string name="story37text">A Beetle once begged the Eagle to spare a Hare which had run to her for protection. But the Eagle pounced upon her prey, the sweep of her great wings tumbling the Beetle a dozen feet away. Furious at the disrespect shown her, the Beetle flew to the Eagle\'s nest and rolled out the eggs. Not one did she spare. The Eagle\'s grief and anger knew no bounds, but who had done the cruel deed she did not know.\n\nNext year the Eagle built her nest far up on a mountain crag; but the Beetle found it and again destroyed the eggs. In despair the Eagle now implored great Jupiter to let her place her eggs in his lap. There none would dare harm them. But the Beetle buzzed about Jupiter\'s head, and made him rise to drive her away; and the eggs rolled from his lap.\n\nNow the Beetle told the reason for her action, and Jupiter had to acknowledge the justice of her cause. And they say that ever after, while the Eagle\'s eggs lie in the nest in spring, the Beetle still sleeps in the ground. For so Jupiter commanded.\n\nMoral: Even the weakest may find means to avenge a wrong.</string>
    <string name="story38text">Early one morning a hungry Wolf was prowling around a cottage at the edge of a village, when he heard a child crying in the house. Then he heard the Mother\'s voice say:\n\n\"Hush, child, hush! Stop your crying, or I will give you to the Wolf!\"\n\nSurprised but delighted at the prospect of so delicious a meal, the Wolf settled down under an open window, expecting every moment to have the child handed out to him. But though the little one continued to fret, the Wolf waited all day in vain. Then, toward nightfall, he heard the Mother\'s voice again as she sat down near the window to sing and rock her baby to sleep.\n\n\"There, child, there! The Wolf shall not get you. No, no! Daddy is watching and Daddy will kill him if he should come near!\"\n\nJust then the Father came within sight of the home, and the Wolf was barely able to save himself from the Dogs by a clever bit of running.\n\nMoral: Do not believe everything you hear.</string>
    <string name="story39text">A Dog, to whom the butcher had thrown a bone, was hurrying home with his prize as fast as he could go. As he crossed a narrow footbridge, he happened to look down and saw himself reflected in the quiet water as if in a mirror. But the greedy Dog thought he saw a real Dog carrying a bone much bigger than his own.\n\nIf he had stopped to think he would have known better. But instead of thinking, he dropped his bone and sprang at the Dog in the river, only to find himself swimming for dear life to reach the shore. At last he managed to scramble out, and as he stood sadly thinking about the good bone he had lost, he realized what a stupid Dog he had been.\n\nMoral: It is very foolish to be greedy.</string>

</resources>