<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BedtimeStories</string>
    <string name="story0text">A shepherd-boy, who watched a flock of sheep near a village, brought out the villagers three or four times by crying out, \"Wolf! Wolf!\" and when his neighbors came to help him, laughed at them for their pains.\n\nThe Wolf, however, did truly come at last. The Shepherd-boy, now really alarmed, shouted in an agony of terror: \"Pray, do come and help me; the Wolf is killing the sheep\"; but no one paid any heed to his cries, nor rendered any assistance. The Wolf, having no cause of fear, at his leisure lacerated or destroyed the whole flock.\n\nThere is no believing a liar, even when he speaks the truth.</string>
    <string name="story1text">An old man on the point of death summoned his sons around him to give them some parting advice. He ordered his servants to bring in a bundle of sticks, and said to his eldest son, \"Break it.\" The son strained and strained, but with all his efforts was unable to break the bundle. The other sons also tried, but none of them was successful. \"Untie the bundle,\" said the father, \"and each of you take a stick.\" When they had done so, he called out to them, \"Now, break,\" and each stick was easily broken. \"You see my meaning,\" said their father.</string>
    <string name="story2text">A Fox once saw a Crow fly off with a piece of cheese in its beak and settle on a branch of a tree.\n\n\"That\'s for me, as I am a Fox,\" said Master Reynard, and he walked up to the foot of the tree.\n\n\"Good day, Mistress Crow,\" he cried. \"How well you are looking today: how glossy your feathers; how bright your eye. I feel sure your voice must surpass that of other birds, just as your figure does; let me hear but one song from you that I may greet you as the Queen of Birds.\"\n\nThe Crow lifted up her head and began to caw her best, but the moment she opened her mouth the piece of cheese fell to the ground, only to be snapped up by Master Fox.\n\n\"That will do,\" said he. \"That was all I wanted. In exchange for your cheese I will give you a piece of advice for the future: \"Do not trust flatterers.\"</string>
    <string name="story3text">Once when a Lion was asleep a little Mouse began running up and down upon him; this soon wakened the Lion, who placed his huge paw upon him, and opened his big jaws to swallow him. \"Pardon, O King,\" cried the little Mouse: \"forgive me this time, I shall never forget it: who knows but what I may be able to do you a turn some of these days?\" The Lion was so tickled at the idea of the Mouse being able to help him, that he lifted up his paw and let him go.\n\nSome time after the Lion was caught in a trap, and the hunters who desired to carry him alive to the King, tied him to a tree while they went in search of a waggon to carry him on. Just then the little Mouse happened to pass by, and seeing the sad plight in which the Lion was, went up to him and soon gnawed away the ropes that bound the King of the Beasts. \"Was I not right?\" said the little Mouse.</string>
    <string name="story4text">The Hare was once boasting of his speed before the other animals. \"I have never yet been beaten,\" said he, \"when I put forth my full speed. I challenge any one here to race with me.\"\n\nThe Tortoise said quietly, \"I accept your challenge.\"\n\n\"That is a good joke,\" said the Hare; \"I could dance round you all the way.\"\n\n\"Keep your boasting till you\'ve won,\" answered the Tortoise. \"Shall we race?\"\n\nSo a course was fixed and a start was made. The Hare darted almost out of sight at once, but soon stopped and, to show his contempt for the Tortoise, lay down to have a nap. The Tortoise plodded on and plodded on, and when the Hare awoke from his nap, he saw the Tortoise just near the winning-post and could not run up in time to save the race.\n\nThen the Tortoise said: \"Slow but steady progress wins the race.\"</string>
    <string name="story5text">The Wind and the Sun were disputing which was the stronger. Suddenly they saw a traveller coming down the road, and the Sun said, \"I see a way to decide our dispute. Whichever of us can cause that traveller to take off his cloak shall be regarded as the stronger. You begin.\" So the Sun retired behind a cloud, and the Wind began to blow as hard as it could upon the traveller. But the harder he blew the more closely did the traveller wrap his cloak round him, till at last the Wind had to give up in despair. Then the Sun came out and shone in all his glory upon the traveller, who soon found it too hot to walk with his cloak on.</string>
    <string name="story6text">A Wolf found great difficulty in getting at the sheep owing to the vigilance of the shepherd and his dogs. But one day it found the skin of a sheep that had been flayed and thrown aside, so it put it on over its own pelt and strolled down among the sheep.\n\nThe Lamb that belonged to the sheep whose skin the Wolf was wearing began to follow the Wolf in the Sheep\'s clothing. So, leading the Lamb a little apart, he soon made a meal off her - and for some time he succeeded in deceiving the sheep, and enjoying hearty meals.\n\nAppearances are deceptive.</string>
    <string name="story7text">Once upon a time there was a dear little girl who was loved by everyone who looked at her, but most of all by her grandmother, and there was nothing that she would not have given to the child. Once she gave her a little riding hood of red velvet, which suited her so well that she would never wear anything else; so she was always called \'Little Red Riding Hood.\'\n\nOne day her mother said to her: \'Come, Little Red Riding Hood, here is a piece of cake and a bottle of wine; take them to your grandmother, she is ill and weak, and they will do her good. Set out before it gets hot, and when you are going, walk nicely and quietly and do not run off the path, or you may fall and break the bottle, and then your grandmother will get nothing; and when you go into her room, don\'t forget to say, \"Good morning\", and don\'t peep into every corner before you do it.\'\n\n\'I will take great care,\' said Little Red Riding Hood to her mother, and gave her hand on it.\n\nThe grandmother lived out in the wood, half a league from the village, and just as Little Red Riding Hood entered the wood, a wolf met her. Red Riding Hood did not know what a wicked creature he was, and was not at all afraid of him.\n\n\'Good day, Little Red Riding Hood,\' said he.\n\n\'Thank you kindly, wolf.\'\n\n\'Whither away so early, Little Red Riding Hood?\'\n\n\'To my grandmother\'s.\'\n\n\'What have you got in your apron?\'\n\n\'Cake and wine; yesterday was baking-day, so poor sick grandmother is to have something good, to make her stronger.\'\n\n\'Where does your grandmother live, Little Red Riding Hood?\'\n\n\'A good quarter of a league farther on in the wood; her house stands under the three large oak-trees, the nut-trees are just below; you surely must know it,\' replied Little Red Riding Hood.\n\nThe wolf thought to himself: \'What a tender young creature! what a nice plump mouthful - she will be better to eat than the old woman. I must act craftily, so as to catch both.\'\n\nSo he walked for a short time by the side of Little Red Riding Hood, and then he said: \'See, Little Red Riding Hood, how pretty the flowers are about here - why do you not look round? I believe, too, that you do not hear how sweetly the little birds are singing; you walk gravely along as if you were going to school, while everything else out here in the wood is merry.\'\n\nLittle Red Riding Hood raised her eyes, and when she saw the sunbeams dancing here and there through the trees, and pretty flowers growing everywhere, she thought: \'Suppose I take grandmother a fresh nosegay; that would please her too. It is so early in the day that I shall still get there in good time.\'\n\nSo she ran from the path into the wood to look for flowers. And whenever she had picked one, she fancied that she saw a still prettier one farther on, and ran after it, and so got deeper and deeper into the wood.\n\nMeanwhile the wolf ran straight to the grandmother\'s house and knocked at the door.\n\n\'Who is there?\'\n\n\'Little Red Riding Hood,\' replied the wolf. \'She is bringing cake and wine; open the door.\'\n\n\'Lift the latch,\' called out the grandmother, \'I am too weak, and cannot get up.\'\n\nThe wolf lifted the latch, the door sprang open, and without saying a word he went straight to the grandmother\'s bed, and devoured her. Then he put on her clothes, dressed himself in her cap, laid himself in bed and drew the curtains.\n\nLittle Red Riding Hood, however, had been running about picking flowers, and when she had gathered so many that she could carry no more, she remembered her grandmother, and set out on the way to her.\n\nShe was surprised to find the cottage-door standing open, and when she went into the room, she had such a strange feeling that she said to herself: \'Oh dear! how uneasy I feel today, and at other times I like being with grandmother so much.\' She called out: \'Good morning,\' but received no answer; so she went to the bed and drew back the curtains. There lay her grandmother with her cap pulled far over her face, and looking very strange.\n\n\'Oh! grandmother,\' she said, \'what big ears you have!\'\n\n\'All the better to hear you with, my child,\' was the reply.\n\n\'But, grandmother, what big eyes you have!\' she said.\n\n\'All the better to see you with, my dear.\'\n\n\'But, grandmother, what large hands you have!\'\n\n\'All the better to hug you with.\'\n\n\'Oh! but, grandmother, what a terrible big mouth you have!\'\n\n\'All the better to eat you with!\'\n\nAnd scarcely had the wolf said this, than with one bound he was out of bed and swallowed up Red Riding Hood.\n\nWhen the wolf had appeased his appetite, he lay down again in the bed, fell asleep and began to snore very loud.\n\nThe huntsman was just passing the house, and thought to himself: \'How the old woman is snoring! I must just see if she wants anything.\' So he went into the room, and when he came to the bed, he saw that the wolf was lying in it.\n\n\'Do I find you here, you old sinner!\' said he. \'I have long sought you!\' But just as he was going to fire at him, it occurred to him that the wolf might have devoured the grandmother, and that she might still be saved, so he did not fire, but took a pair of scissors, and began to cut open the stomach of the sleeping wolf.\n\nWhen he had made two snips, he saw the little red riding hood shining, and then he made two snips more, and the little girl sprang out, crying: \'Ah, how frightened I have been! How dark it was inside the wolf.\'\n\nAfter that the aged grandmother came out alive also, but scarcely able to breathe. Red Riding Hood, however, quickly fetched great stones with which they filled the wolf\'s belly, and when he awoke, he wanted to run away, but the stones were so heavy that he collapsed at once, and fell dead.\n\nThen all three were delighted. The huntsman drew off the wolf\'s skin and went home with it; the grandmother ate the cake and drank the wine which Red Riding Hood had brought, and revived. But Red Riding Hood thought to herself: \'As long as I live, I will never leave the path by myself to run into the wood, when my mother has forbidden me to do so.\'\n\nIt is also related that once, when Red Riding Hood was again taking cakes to the old grandmother, another wolf spoke to her, and tried to entice her from the path. Red Riding Hood, however, was on her guard, and went straight forward on her way, and told her grandmother that she had met the wolf, and that he had said \'good morning\' to her, but with such a wicked look in his eyes, that if they had not been on the public road she was certain he would have eaten her up.\n\n\'Well,\' said the grandmother, \'we will shut the door, so that he can not come in.\'\n\nSoon afterwards the wolf knocked, and cried: \'Open the door, grandmother, I am Little Red Riding Hood, and am bringing you some cakes.\'\n\nBut they did not speak, or open the door, so the grey-beard stole twice or thrice round the house, and at last jumped on the roof, intending to wait until Red Riding Hood went home in the evening, and then to steal after her and devour her in the darkness. But the grandmother saw what was in his thoughts.\n\nIn front of the house was a great stone trough, so she said to the child: \'Take the pail, Red Riding Hood; I made some sausages yesterday, so carry the water in which I boiled them to the trough.\'\n\nRed Riding Hood carried until the great trough was quite full. Then the smell of the sausages reached the wolf, and he sniffed and peeped down, and at last stretched out his neck so far that he could no longer keep his footing and began to slip, and slipped down from the roof straight into the great trough, and was drowned. But Red Riding Hood went joyously home, and no one ever did anything to harm her again.</string>
    <string name="story8text">There were once a man and a woman who had long, in vain, wished for a child. At length it appeared that God was about to grant their desire.\n\nThese people had a little window at the back of their house from which a splendid garden could be seen, which was full of the most beautiful flowers and herbs. It was, however, surrounded by a high wall, and no one dared to go into it because it belonged to an enchantress, who had great power and was dreaded by all the world.\n\nOne day the woman was standing by this window and looking down into the garden, when she saw a bed which was planted with the most beautiful rampion, and it looked so fresh and green that she longed for it. She quite pined away, and began to look pale and miserable.\n\nHer husband was alarmed, and asked: \'What ails you, dear wife?\'\n\n\'Ah,\' she replied, \'if I can\'t eat some of the rampion, which is in the garden behind our house, I shall die.\'\n\nThe man, who loved her, thought: \'Sooner than let your wife die, bring her some of the rampion yourself, let it cost what it will.\'\n\nAt twilight, he clambered down over the wall into the garden of the enchantress, hastily clutched a handful of rampion, and took it to his wife. She at once made herself a salad of it, and ate it greedily. It tasted so good to her - so very good, that the next day she longed for it three times as much as before.\n\nIf he was to have any rest, her husband knew he must once more descend into the garden. Therefore, in the gloom of evening, he let himself down again; but when he had clambered down the wall he was terribly afraid, for he saw the enchantress standing before him.\n\n\'How can you dare,\' said she with angry look, \'descend into my garden and steal my rampion like a thief? You shall suffer for it!\'\n\n\'Ah,\' answered he, \'let mercy take the place of justice, I only made up my mind to do it out of necessity. My wife saw your rampion from the window, and felt such a longing for it that she would have died if she had not got some to eat.\'\n\nThe enchantress allowed her anger to be softened, and said to him: \'If the case be as you say, I will allow you to take away with you as much rampion as you will, only I make one condition, you must give me the child which your wife will bring into the world; it shall be well treated, and I will care for it like a mother.\'\n\nThe man in his terror consented to everything.\n\nWhen the woman was brought to bed, the enchantress appeared at once, gave the child the name of Rapunzel, and took it away with her.\n\nRapunzel grew into the most beautiful child under the sun. When she was twelve years old, the enchantress shut her into a tower in the middle of a forest. The tower had neither stairs nor door, but near the top was a little window. When the enchantress wanted to go in, she placed herself beneath it and cried:\n\n\'Rapunzel, Rapunzel,\nLet down your hair to me.\'\nRapunzel had magnificent long hair, fine as spun gold, and when she heard the voice of the enchantress, she unfastened her braided tresses, wound them round one of the hooks of the window above, and then the hair fell twenty ells down, and the enchantress climbed up by it.\n\nAfter a year or two, it came to pass that the king\'s son rode through the forest and passed by the tower. Then he heard a song, which was so charming that he stood still and listened. It was Rapunzel, who in her solitude passed her time in letting her sweet voice resound. The king\'s son wanted to climb up to her, and looked for the door of the tower, but none was to be found. He rode home, but the singing had so deeply touched his heart, that every day he went out into the forest and listened to it.\n\nOnce when he was thus standing behind a tree, he saw that an enchantress came there, and he heard how she cried:\n\n\'Rapunzel, Rapunzel,\nLet down your hair to me.\'\nThen Rapunzel let down the braids of her hair, and the enchantress climbed up to her.\n\n\'If that is the ladder by which one mounts, I too will try my fortune,\' said he, and the next day when it began to grow dark, he went to the tower and cried:\n\n\'Rapunzel, Rapunzel,\nLet down your hair to me.\'\nImmediately the hair fell down and the king\'s son climbed up.\n\nAt first Rapunzel was terribly frightened when a man, such as her eyes had never yet beheld, came to her; but the king\'s son began to talk to her quite like a friend, and told her that his heart had been so stirred that it had let him have no rest, and he had been forced to see her. Then Rapunzel lost her fear, and when he asked her if she would take him for her husband, and she saw that he was young and handsome, she thought: \'He will love me more than old Dame Gothel does\'; and she said yes, and laid her hand in his.\n\nShe said: \'I will willingly go away with you, but I do not know how to get down. Bring with you a skein of silk every time that you come, and I will weave a ladder with it, and when that is ready I will descend, and you will take me on your horse.\'\n\nThey agreed that until that time he should come to her every evening, for the old woman came by day. The enchantress remarked nothing of this, until once Rapunzel said to her: \'Tell me, Dame Gothel, how it happens that you are so much heavier for me to draw up than the young king\'s son - he is with me in a moment.\'\n\n\'Ah! you wicked child,\' cried the enchantress. \'What do I hear you say! I thought I had separated you from all the world, and yet you have deceived me!\'\n\nIn her anger she clutched Rapunzel\'s beautiful tresses, wrapped them twice round her left hand, seized a pair of scissors with the right, and snip, snap, they were cut off, and the lovely braids lay on the ground. And she was so pitiless that she took poor Rapunzel into a desert where she had to live in great grief and misery.\n\nOn the same day that she cast out Rapunzel, however, the enchantress fastened the braids of hair, which she had cut off, to the hook of the window, and when the king\'s son came and cried:\n\n\'Rapunzel, Rapunzel,\nLet down your hair to me.\'\nShe let the hair down. The king\'s son ascended, but instead of finding his dearest Rapunzel, he found the enchantress, who gazed at him with wicked and venomous looks.\n\n\'Aha!\' she cried mockingly, \'you would fetch your dearest, but the beautiful bird sits no longer singing in the nest; the cat has got it, and will scratch out your eyes as well. Rapunzel is lost to you; you will never see her again.\'\n\nThe king\'s son was beside himself with pain, and in his despair he leapt down from the tower. He escaped with his life, but the thorns into which he fell pierced his eyes.\n\nHe wandered quite blind about the forest, ate nothing but roots and berries, and did naught but lament and weep over the loss of his dearest wife. Thus he roamed about in misery for some years, and at length came to the desert where Rapunzel, with the twins to which she had given birth, a boy and a girl, lived in wretchedness. He heard a voice, and it seemed so familiar to him that he went towards it, and when he approached, Rapunzel knew him and fell on his neck and wept. Two of her tears wetted his eyes and they grew clear again, and he could see with them as before. He led her to his kingdom where he was joyfully received, and they lived for a long time afterwards, happy and contented.</string>
    <string name="story9text">Once there was a miller who was poor, but who had a beautiful daughter. Now it happened that he had to go and speak to the king, and in order to make himself appear important he said to him, \"I have a daughter who can spin straw into gold.\"\n\nThe king said to the miller, \"That is an art which pleases me well, if your daughter is as clever as you say, bring her to-morrow to my palace, and I will put her to the test.\"\n\nAnd when the girl was brought to him he took her into a room which was quite full of straw, gave her a spinning-wheel and a reel, and said, \"Now set to work, and if by to-morrow morning early you have not spun this straw into gold during the night, you must die.\"\n\nThereupon he himself locked up the room, and left her in it alone. So there sat the poor miller\'s daughter, and for the life of her could not tell what to do, she had no idea how straw could be spun into gold, and she grew more and more frightened, until at last she began to weep.\n\nBut all at once the door opened, and in came a little man, and said, \"Good evening, mistress miller, why are you crying so?\"\n\n\"Alas,\" answered the girl, \"I have to spin straw into gold, and I do not know how to do it.\"\n\n\"What will you give me,\" said the manikin, \"if I do it for you?\"\n\n\"My necklace,\" said the girl.\n\nThe little man took the necklace, seated himself in front of the wheel, and whirr, whirr, whirr, three turns, and the reel was full, then he put another on, and whirr, whirr, whirr, three times round, and the second was full too. And so it went on until the morning, when all the straw was spun, and all the reels were full of gold.\n\nBy daybreak the king was already there, and when he saw the gold he was astonished and delighted, but his heart became only more greedy. He had the miller\'s daughter taken into another room full of straw, which was much larger, and commanded her to spin that also in one night if she valued her life. The girl knew not how to help herself, and was crying, when the door opened again, and the little man appeared, and said, \"What will you give me if I spin that straw into gold for you?\"\n\n\"The ring on my finger,\" answered the girl.\n\nThe little man took the ring, again began to turn the wheel, and by morning had spun all the straw into glittering gold.\n\nThe king rejoiced beyond measure at the sight, but still he had not gold enough, and he had the miller\'s daughter taken into a still larger room full of straw, and said, \"You must spin this, too, in the course of this night, but if you succeed, you shall be my wife.\"\n\nEven if she be a miller\'s daughter, thought he, I could not find a richer wife in the whole world.\n\nWhen the girl was alone the manikin came again for the third time, and said, \"What will you give me if I spin the straw for you this time also?\"\n\n\"I have nothing left that I could give,\" answered the girl.\n\n\"Then promise me, if you should become queen, to give me your first child.\"\n\nWho knows whether that will ever happen, thought the miller\'s daughter, and, not knowing how else to help herself in this strait, she promised the manikin what he wanted, and for that he once more spun the straw into gold.\n\nAnd when the king came in the morning, and found all as he had wished, he took her in marriage, and the pretty miller\'s daughter became a queen.\n\nA year after, she brought a beautiful child into the world, and she never gave a thought to the manikin. But suddenly he came into her room, and said, \"Now give me what you promised.\"\n\nThe queen was horror-struck, and offered the manikin all the riches of the kingdom if he would leave her the child. But the manikin said, \"No, something alive is dearer to me than all the treasures in the world.\"\n\nThen the queen began to lament and cry, so that the manikin pitied her.\n\n\"I will give you three days, time,\" said he, \"if by that time you find out my name, then shall you keep your child.\"\n\nSo the queen thought the whole night of all the names that she had ever heard, and she sent a messenger over the country to inquire, far and wide, for any other names that there might be. When the manikin came the next day, she began with Caspar, Melchior, Balthazar, and said all the names she knew, one after another, but to every one the little man said, \"That is not my name.\"\n\nOn the second day she had inquiries made in the neighborhood as to the names of the people there, and she repeated to the manikin the most uncommon and curious. Perhaps your name is Shortribs, or Sheepshanks, or Laceleg, but he always answered, \"That is not my name.\"\n\nOn the third day the messenger came back again, and said, \"I have not been able to find a single new name, but as I came to a high mountain at the end of the forest, where the fox and the hare bid each other good night, there I saw a little house, and before the house a fire was burning, and round about the fire quite a ridiculous little man was jumping, he hopped upon one leg, and shouted –\n\n\'To-day I bake, to-morrow brew,\nthe next I\'ll have the young queen\'s child.\nHa, glad am I that no one knew\nthat Rumpelstiltskin I am styled.\'\"\nYou may imagine how glad the queen was when she heard the name. And when soon afterwards the little man came in, and asked, \"Now, mistress queen, what is my name?\"\n\nAt first she said, \"Is your name Conrad?\"\n\n\"No.\"\n\n\"Is your name Harry?\"\n\n\"No.\"\n\n\"Perhaps your name is Rumpelstiltskin?\"\n\n\"The devil has told you that! The devil has told you that,\" cried the little man, and in his anger he plunged his right foot so deep into the earth that his whole leg went in, and then in rage he pulled at his left leg so hard with both hands that he tore himself in two.</string>
    <string name="story10text">One fine evening a young princess put on her bonnet and clogs, and went out to take a walk by herself in a wood; and when she came to a cool spring of water with a rose in the middle of it, she sat herself down to rest a while. Now she had a golden ball in her hand, which was her favourite plaything; and she was always tossing it up into the air, and catching it again as it fell.\n\nAfter a time she threw it up so high that she missed catching it as it fell; and the ball bounded away, and rolled along on the ground, until at last it fell down into the spring. The princess looked into the spring after her ball, but it was very deep, so deep that she could not see the bottom of it. She began to cry, and said, \'Alas! if I could only get my ball again, I would give all my fine clothes and jewels, and everything that I have in the world.\'\n\nWhilst she was speaking, a frog put its head out of the water, and said, \'Princess, why do you weep so bitterly?\'\n\n\'Alas!\' said she, \'what can you do for me, you nasty frog? My golden ball has fallen into the spring.\'\n\nThe frog said, \'I do not want your pearls, and jewels, and fine clothes; but if you will love me, and let me live with you and eat from off your golden plate, and sleep on your bed, I will bring you your ball again.\'\n\n\'What nonsense,\' thought the princess, \'this silly frog is talking! He can never even get out of the spring to visit me, though he may be able to get my ball for me, and therefore I will tell him he shall have what he asks.\'\n\nSo she said to the frog, \'Well, if you will bring me my ball, I will do all you ask.\'\n\nThen the frog put his head down, and dived deep under the water; and after a little while he came up again, with the ball in his mouth, and threw it on the edge of the spring.\n\nAs soon as the young princess saw her ball, she ran to pick it up; and she was so overjoyed to have it in her hand again, that she never thought of the frog, but ran home with it as fast as she could.\n\nThe frog called after her, \'Stay, princess, and take me with you as you said,\'\n\nBut she did not stop to hear a word.\n\nThe next day, just as the princess had sat down to dinner, she heard a strange noise - tap, tap - plash, plash - as if something was coming up the marble staircase, and soon afterwards there was a gentle knock at the door, and a little voice cried out and said:\n\n\'Open the door, my princess dear,\nOpen the door to thy true love here!\nAnd mind the words that thou and I said\nBy the fountain cool, in the greenwood shade.\'\nThen the princess ran to the door and opened it, and there she saw the frog, whom she had quite forgotten. At this sight she was sadly frightened, and shutting the door as fast as she could came back to her seat.\n\nThe king, her father, seeing that something had frightened her, asked her what was the matter.\n\n\'There is a nasty frog,\' said she, \'at the door, that lifted my ball for me out of the spring this morning. I told him that he should live with me here, thinking that he could never get out of the spring; but there he is at the door, and he wants to come in.\'\n\nWhile she was speaking the frog knocked again at the door, and said:\n\n\'Open the door, my princess dear,\nOpen the door to thy true love here!\nAnd mind the words that thou and I said\nBy the fountain cool, in the greenwood shade.\'\nThen the king said to the young princess, \'As you have given your word you must keep it; so go and let him in.\'\n\nShe did so, and the frog hopped into the room, and then straight on - tap, tap - plash, plash - from the bottom of the room to the top, till he came up close to the table where the princess sat.\n\n\'Pray lift me upon chair,\' said he to the princess, \'and let me sit next to you.\'\n\nAs soon as she had done this, the frog said, \'Put your plate nearer to me, that I may eat out of it.\'\n\nThis she did, and when he had eaten as much as he could, he said, \'Now I am tired; carry me upstairs, and put me into your bed.\' And the princess, though very unwilling, took him up in her hand, and put him upon the pillow of her own bed, where he slept all night long.\n\nAs soon as it was light the frog jumped up, hopped downstairs, and went out of the house.\n\n\'Now, then,\' thought the princess, \'at last he is gone, and I shall be troubled with him no more.\'\n\nBut she was mistaken; for when night came again she heard the same tapping at the door; and the frog came once more, and said:\n\n\'Open the door, my princess dear,\nOpen the door to thy true love here!\nAnd mind the words that thou and I said\nBy the fountain cool, in the greenwood shade.\'\nAnd when the princess opened the door the frog came in, and slept upon her pillow as before, till the morning broke. And the third night he did the same. But when the princess awoke on the following morning she was astonished to see, instead of the frog, a handsome prince, gazing on her with the most beautiful eyes she had ever seen and standing at the head of her bed.\n\nHe told her that he had been enchanted by a spiteful fairy, who had changed him into a frog; and that he had been fated so to abide till some princess should take him out of the spring, and let him eat from her plate, and sleep upon her bed for three nights.\n\n\'You,\' said the prince, \'have broken his cruel charm, and now I have nothing to wish for but that you should go with me into my father\'s kingdom, where I will marry you, and love you as long as you live.\'\n\nThe young princess, you may be sure, was not long in saying \'Yes\' to all this; and as they spoke a brightly coloured coach drove up, with eight beautiful horses, decked with plumes of feathers and a golden harness; and behind the coach rode the prince\'s servant, faithful Heinrich, who had bewailed the misfortunes of his dear master during his enchantment so long and so bitterly, that his heart had well-nigh burst.\n\nThey then took leave of the king, and got into the coach with eight horses, and all set out, full of joy and merriment, for the prince\'s kingdom, which they reached safely; and there they lived happily a great many years.</string>
    <string name="story11text">Text of story 11</string>
    <string name="story12text">Text of story 12</string>
    <string name="story13text">Text of story 13</string>
    <string name="story14text">Text of story 14</string>
    <string name="story15text">Text of story 15</string>
    <string name="story16text">Text of story 16</string>
    <string name="story17text">Text of story 17</string>
    <string name="story18text">Text of story 18</string>
    <string name="story19text">Text of story 19</string>
    <string name="story20text">Text of story 20</string>
    <string name="story21text">Text of story 21</string>
    <string name="story22text">Text of story 22</string>
    <string name="story23text">Text of story 23</string>
    <string name="story24text">Text of story 24</string>
    <string name="story25text">Text of story 25</string>
    <string name="story26text">Text of story 26</string>
    <string name="story27text">Text of story 27</string>
    <string name="story28text">Text of story 28</string>
    <string name="story29text">Text of story 29</string>
</resources>